{"id": 0, "question": " I'd like either a soft drink or a refreshing bottled beverage delivered to my spot at the third table.", "answer": "On_Softdrink_Table3 | On_BottledDrink_Table3", "ctxs": [{"id": "98", "title": "Reach for the apple on the counter and take a bite.", "text": "grab_Apple", "score": "2.3269172"}, {"id": "99", "title": "Put the salad bowl back in the fridge to keep it fresh.", "text": "put_Salad_Fridge", "score": "1.7989146"}, {"id": "19", "title": "Sit at the coffee table and enjoy your coffee.", "text": "sit_Coffee_table", "score": "1.6897022"}]}
{"id": 1, "question": "It's too dark here. Can you turn on the tube light or the hall light?", "answer": "Active_TubeLight | Active_HallLight", "ctxs": [{"id": "103", "title": "Sit on the sofa and relax while watching your favorite TV show.", "text": "sit_Sofa", "score": "1.8130138"}, {"id": "100", "title": "Touch the vase on the shelf and admire its design.", "text": "touch_Vase", "score": "1.7896893"}, {"id": "102", "title": "Switch off the lights before leaving the room to save energy.", "text": "switchoff_LightSwitch", "score": "1.7855375"}]}
{"id": 2, "question": "The floor seems a bit dusty, could you give it a good sweep? Also, I'd love a refreshing bottled beverage at Table 1 when you have a moment", "answer": "IsClean_Floor & On_BottledDrink_Table1", "ctxs": [{"id": "98", "title": "Reach for the apple on the counter and take a bite.", "text": "grab_Apple", "score": "1.5514145"}, {"id": "99", "title": "Put the salad bowl back in the fridge to keep it fresh.", "text": "put_Salad_Fridge", "score": "1.4555775"}, {"id": "1", "title": "Before you leave, could you turn off the stove?", "text": "switchoff_Stove", "score": "1.3891491"}]}
{"id": 3, "question": "Can you serve chocolate at the bright sixth table or bring some chips to the second table?", "answer": "On_Chocolate_WindowTable6 | On_Chips_Table2", "ctxs": [{"id": "68", "title": "Grab a BellPepper for the salad.", "text": "grab_BellPepper", "score": "1.5805817"}, {"id": "104", "title": "Take a peach from the fruit basket and enjoy its sweetness.", "text": "grab_Peach", "score": "1.5152838"}, {"id": "23", "title": "Touch the photo frame on the wall to straighten it.", "text": "touch_PhotoFrame", "score": "1.4854928"}]}
{"id": 4, "question": "I'm sitting at the third table, could you please bring me either some fries or a dessert?", "answer": "On_Chips_Table3 | On_Dessert_Table3", "ctxs": [{"id": "23", "title": "Touch the photo frame on the wall to straighten it.", "text": "touch_PhotoFrame", "score": "1.7196392"}, {"id": "91", "title": "Take a carrot from the vegetable basket and start cooking.", "text": "grab_Carrot", "score": "1.5957652"}, {"id": "59", "title": "After breakfast, put the Bread in the Bread box to keep it fresh.", "text": "put_Bread_Box", "score": "1.5957651"}]}
{"id": 5, "question": "Everything is so dirty here, please wipe down the table and mop the floor.", "answer": "IsClean_Table1 & IsClean_Floor", "ctxs": [{"id": "95", "title": "Before starting dinner, grab a plate from the cupboard.", "text": "grab_Plate", "score": "1.4283926"}, {"id": "3", "title": "After preparing breakfast, put the milk back in the fridge.", "text": "put_Milk_Fridge", "score": "1.4036481"}, {"id": "110", "title": "Lower the heating and clean the floor please.", "text": "Low_ACTemperature & IsClean_Floor", "score": "1.3481021"}]}
{"id": 6, "question": " I dropped my vacuum cup, could you pick it up and hold it? And also, bring a milk drink to the second table.", "answer": "Holding_VacuumCup & On_MilkDrink_Table2", "ctxs": [{"id": "104", "title": "Take a peach from the fruit basket and enjoy its sweetness.", "text": "grab_Peach", "score": "1.9651835"}, {"id": "0", "title": "Can you walk towards the wall phone and answer it?", "text": "walktowards_Wall_phone", "score": "1.5946069"}, {"id": "10", "title": "Touch the curtains to see if they need cleaning.", "text": "touch_Curtains", "score": "1.4832749"}]}
{"id": 7, "question": "Please turn on the AC and bring me Juice to Bar.", "answer": "Active_AC & On_NFCJuice_Bar", "ctxs": [{"id": "108", "title": "Before going to bed, switch off the wall lamp.", "text": "switchoff_Wall_lamp", "score": "2.625446"}, {"id": "107", "title": "Enjoy a glass of beer from the fridge after a long day.", "text": "drink_Beer", "score": "2.2202952"}, {"id": "25", "title": "Sit at the nightstand and read a book before sleeping.", "text": "sit_Nightstand", "score": "2.0412"}]}
{"id": 8, "question": "Can you lower the heating and check if there are any dessert available?", "answer": "Low_ACTemperature & Exists_Dessert", "ctxs": [{"id": "109", "title": "Lower the heating and check if there are any dessert prepared?", "text": "Low_ACTemperature & Exists_Dessert", "score": "2.255676"}, {"id": "2", "title": "As you walk in, please grab a towel to wipe the table.", "text": "grab_PaperTowel", "score": "1.5204227"}, {"id": "59", "title": "After breakfast, put the Bread in the Bread box to keep it fresh.", "text": "put_Bread_Box", "score": "1.3213528"}]}
{"id": 9, "question": "It's so hot. I want to close the curtains and turn on the air conditioning.", "answer": "Closed_Curtain & Active_AC", "ctxs": [{"id": "114", "title": "Close the curtains and the air conditioning.", "text": "Closed_Curtain & Closed_AC", "score": "1.7623174"}, {"id": "115", "title": "Open the curtains and the air conditioning.", "text": "Activate_Curtain & Activate_AC", "score": "1.72641"}, {"id": "2", "title": "As you walk in, please grab a towel to wipe the table.", "text": "grab_PaperTowel", "score": "1.3044966"}]}
{"id": 10, "question": "Would you kindly proceed to either bar 2 or the main bar?", "answer": "RobotNear_Bar2 | RobotNear_Bar", "ctxs": [{"id": "116", "title": "Could you come to either the bar or the first table?", "text": "RobotNear_Bar | RobotNear_Table1", "score": "1.5414981"}, {"id": "108", "title": "Before going to bed, switch off the wall lamp.", "text": "switchoff_Wall_lamp", "score": "1.267693"}]}
{"id": 11, "question": "Can you send a cup of coffee and dessert to table 3?", "answer": "On_Coffee_Table3 & On_Dessert_Table3", "ctxs": [{"id": "23", "title": "Touch the photo frame on the wall to straighten it.", "text": "touch_PhotoFrame", "score": "1.9396284"}, {"id": "85", "title": "Turn the light switch on before entering the dark room.", "text": "switchon_LightSwitch", "score": "1.5959107"}, {"id": "36", "title": "Switch on the LightSwitch before entering the dark room.", "text": "switchon_LightSwitch", "score": "1.5959107"}]}
{"id": 12, "question": "Please place a bottle of spring water on table 2 and turn on the AC since it's warm.", "answer": "On_SpringWater_Table2 & Active_AC", "ctxs": [{"id": "8", "title": "Put the dirty dish bowl in the dishwasher after dinner.", "text": "put_Dish_bowl_Dishwasher", "score": "1.737772"}, {"id": "20", "title": "Grab a carrot and add it to the salad for extra crunch.", "text": "grab_Carrot", "score": "1.7358826"}, {"id": "10", "title": "Touch the curtains to see if they need cleaning.", "text": "touch_Curtains", "score": "1.6949631"}]}
{"id": 13, "question": "Please bring yogurt to table 1 and check if the tube light is working.", "answer": "On_Yogurt_Table1 & Active_TubeLight", "ctxs": [{"id": "22", "title": "Would you mind turning off the wall phone before going to bed?", "text": "switchoff_Wall_phone", "score": "1.7623959"}, {"id": "51", "title": "Switch on the Wall_lamp to brighten up the room.", "text": "switchon_Wall_lamp", "score": "1.7455318"}, {"id": "67", "title": "Switch on the Power_socket to charge your laptop.", "text": "switchon_Power_socket", "score": "1.6950753"}]}
{"id": 14, "question": "Please deliver the yogurt to table number one and turn on the hall light.", "answer": "On_Yogurt_Table1 & Active_HallLight", "ctxs": [{"id": "24", "title": "Put the wine glasses back in the cabinet after the party.", "text": "put_WineGlass_Cabinet", "score": "1.9315922"}, {"id": "42", "title": "Before bed, make sure to switchoff the bedside wall Lamp.", "text": "switchoff_Wall_Lamp", "score": "1.8975685"}, {"id": "6", "title": "Walk towards the apple and take a bite.", "text": "walktowards_Apple", "score": "1.8178573"}]}
{"id": 15, "question": "Please make sure there's either a cup of coffee or a bottled beverage treat ready at Table 2.", "answer": "On_Coffee_Table2 | On_BottledDrink_Table2", "ctxs": [{"id": "41", "title": "Look at the beautiful Wall_phone on your way out.", "text": "lookat_Wall_phone", "score": "1.6607932"}, {"id": "98", "title": "Reach for the apple on the counter and take a bite.", "text": "grab_Apple", "score": "1.6459658"}, {"id": "99", "title": "Put the salad bowl back in the fridge to keep it fresh.", "text": "put_Salad_Fridge", "score": "1.6308432"}]}
{"id": 16, "question": "Please make sure the water or dessert are ready and available.", "answer": "Exists_Water | Exists_Dessert", "ctxs": [{"id": "41", "title": "Look at the beautiful Wall_phone on your way out.", "text": "lookat_Wall_phone", "score": "1.584352"}, {"id": "59", "title": "After breakfast, put the Bread in the Bread box to keep it fresh.", "text": "put_Bread_Box", "score": "1.4694719"}, {"id": "43", "title": "After washing your hands, touch the PaperTowel to dry off.", "text": "touch_PaperTowel", "score": "1.4694719"}]}
{"id": 17, "question": "Could you bring some chips to Table 1 or a dessert to Window Table 6?", "answer": "On_Chips_Table1 | On_Dessert_WindowTable6", "ctxs": [{"id": "75", "title": "Pour yourself a glass of wine from the bottle on the table.", "text": "drink_Wine", "score": "1.605211"}, {"id": "59", "title": "After breakfast, put the Bread in the Bread box to keep it fresh.", "text": "put_Bread_Box", "score": "1.605211"}, {"id": "43", "title": "After washing your hands, touch the PaperTowel to dry off.", "text": "touch_PaperTowel", "score": "1.605211"}]}
{"id": 18, "question": "Come to table No. 6 by the window and grab my vacuum cup.", "answer": "RobotNear_WindowTable6 & Holding_VacuumCup", "ctxs": [{"id": "0", "title": "Can you walk towards the wall phone and answer it?", "text": "walktowards_Wall_phone", "score": "1.6026961"}, {"id": "10", "title": "Touch the curtains to see if they need cleaning.", "text": "touch_Curtains", "score": "1.398593"}, {"id": "2", "title": "As you walk in, please grab a towel to wipe the table.", "text": "grab_PaperTowel", "score": "1.3359562"}]}
{"id": 19, "question": "Please turn down the air conditioning temperature and tidy up the chairs.", "answer": "Low_ACTemperature & IsClean_Chairs", "ctxs": [{"id": "64", "title": "After dinner, put the Bottle_water back in the fridge.", "text": "put_Bottle_water_Fridge", "score": "1.8059227"}, {"id": "111", "title": "Turn down the temperature and clean the floor.", "text": "Low_ACTemperature & IsClean_Floor", "score": "1.6561537"}, {"id": "81", "title": "Grab a spoon and taste the delicious soup in the pot.", "text": "grab_Spoon", "score": "1.6095219"}]}
{"id": 20, "question": "Please turn up the air conditioning temperature and tidy up the chairs.", "answer": "High_ACTemperature & IsClean_Chairs", "ctxs": [{"id": "64", "title": "After dinner, put the Bottle_water back in the fridge.", "text": "put_Bottle_water_Fridge", "score": "1.732627"}, {"id": "112", "title": "Turn up the temperature and clean the floor.", "text": "High_ACTemperature & IsClean_Floor", "score": "1.6311771"}, {"id": "81", "title": "Grab a spoon and taste the delicious soup in the pot.", "text": "grab_Spoon", "score": "1.602979"}]}
{"id": 21, "question": "Turn on the hall light and clean the floor.", "answer": "Active_HallLight & IsClean_Floor", "ctxs": [{"id": "102", "title": "Switch off the lights before leaving the room to save energy.", "text": "switchoff_LightSwitch", "score": "1.606534"}, {"id": "101", "title": "After preparing breakfast, grab a spoon to eat your cereal.", "text": "grab_Spoon", "score": "1.5795995"}, {"id": "103", "title": "Sit on the sofa and relax while watching your favorite TV show.", "text": "sit_Sofa", "score": "1.5778824"}]}
{"id": 22, "question": "Turn off the hall light and clean the floor.", "answer": "Closed_HallLight & IsClean_Floor", "ctxs": [{"id": "102", "title": "Switch off the lights before leaving the room to save energy.", "text": "switchoff_LightSwitch", "score": "1.7132164"}, {"id": "103", "title": "Sit on the sofa and relax while watching your favorite TV show.", "text": "sit_Sofa", "score": "1.6856155"}, {"id": "101", "title": "After preparing breakfast, grab a spoon to eat your cereal.", "text": "grab_Spoon", "score": "1.6112356"}]}
{"id": 23, "question": "Turn on the tube light and bring chips to Table 3.", "answer": "Active_TubeLight & On_Chips_Table3", "ctxs": [{"id": "42", "title": "Before bed, make sure to switchoff the bedside wall Lamp.", "text": "switchoff_Wall_Lamp", "score": "2.0352967"}, {"id": "74", "title": "Sit on the chair and enjoy a relaxing cup of coffee.", "text": "sit_Chair", "score": "1.9515731"}, {"id": "58", "title": "Walk towards the Wall_lamp and switch it on.", "text": "walktowards_Wall_lamp", "score": "1.9515731"}]}
{"id": 24, "question": "Turn off the tube light and bring chips to Table 3.", "answer": "Closed_TubeLight & On_Chips_Table3", "ctxs": [{"id": "42", "title": "Before bed, make sure to switchoff the bedside wall Lamp.", "text": "switchoff_Wall_Lamp", "score": "2.064149"}, {"id": "74", "title": "Sit on the chair and enjoy a relaxing cup of coffee.", "text": "sit_Chair", "score": "1.9618905"}, {"id": "58", "title": "Walk towards the Wall_lamp and switch it on.", "text": "walktowards_Wall_lamp", "score": "1.9618905"}]}
{"id": 25, "question": "Please close the curtains and bring milk to Table2.", "answer": "Closed_Curtain & On_Milk_Table2", "ctxs": [{"id": "34", "title": "Grab a WineGlass before pouring yourself a glass of wine.", "text": "grab_WineGlass", "score": "1.8793169"}, {"id": "12", "title": "Switch off the TV when you're done watching.", "text": "switchoff_WallTV", "score": "1.7774136"}, {"id": "18", "title": "Look at the beautiful vase on the shelf as you pass by.", "text": "lookat_Vase", "score": "1.7726531"}]}
{"id": 26, "question": "Please open the curtains and bring milk to Table2.", "answer": "Activate_Curtain & On_Milk_Table2", "ctxs": [{"id": "34", "title": "Grab a WineGlass before pouring yourself a glass of wine.", "text": "grab_WineGlass", "score": "1.7756104"}, {"id": "22", "title": "Would you mind turning off the wall phone before going to bed?", "text": "switchoff_Wall_phone", "score": "1.7590755"}, {"id": "104", "title": "Take a peach from the fruit basket and enjoy its sweetness.", "text": "grab_Peach", "score": "1.7019944"}]}
{"id": 27, "question": "Clean the chairs and deliver coffee to the coffee station.", "answer": "IsClean_Chairs & On_Coffee_CoffeeStation", "ctxs": [{"id": "96", "title": "Turn on the wall lamp to create a cozy atmosphere in the room.", "text": "switchon_Wall_lamp", "score": "1.6948644"}, {"id": "95", "title": "Before starting dinner, grab a plate from the cupboard.", "text": "grab_Plate", "score": "1.6470556"}, {"id": "76", "title": "Take a peach from the fruit bowl and enjoy a healthy snack.", "text": "grab_Peach", "score": "1.587671"}]}
{"id": 28, "question": "Could you activate the air cooling system and also bring some yoghurt to the bar?", "answer": "Active_AC & On_Yogurt_Bar", "ctxs": [{"id": "13", "title": "Before leaving, make sure to turn off the light switch.", "text": "switchoff_LightSwitch", "score": "1.4815137"}, {"id": "17", "title": "Pour yourself a glass of wine and unwind.", "text": "drink_Wine", "score": "1.4777615"}, {"id": "107", "title": "Enjoy a glass of beer from the fridge after a long day.", "text": "drink_Beer", "score": "1.4007528"}]}
{"id": 29, "question": "Please make sure the first table is spotless and illuminate the area with the tube light.", "answer": "IsClean_Table1 & Active_TubeLight", "ctxs": [{"id": "72", "title": "Please turn on the stove and start cooking the pancakes.", "text": "switchon_Stove", "score": "1.6875463"}, {"id": "57", "title": "Grab a ChefKnife to chop the vegetables for dinner.", "text": "grab_ChefKnife", "score": "1.6875463"}, {"id": "40", "title": "Can you sit on the Nightstand and read a book?", "text": "sit_Nightstand", "score": "1.6875463"}]}
{"id": 30, "question": "Please bring me coffee or water to table 1.", "answer": "On_Coffee_Table1 | On_Water_Table1", "ctxs": [{"id": "15", "title": "Put the leftover chips in the cabinet to keep them fresh.", "text": "put_Chips_Cabinet", "score": "1.7549331"}, {"id": "23", "title": "Touch the photo frame on the wall to straighten it.", "text": "touch_PhotoFrame", "score": "1.711153"}, {"id": "10", "title": "Touch the curtains to see if they need cleaning.", "text": "touch_Curtains", "score": "1.6819935"}]}
{"id": 31, "question": "Would you mind either tidying up the flooring or delivering a sweet treat to the second table?", "answer": "IsClean_Floor | On_Dessert_Table2", "ctxs": [{"id": "104", "title": "Take a peach from the fruit basket and enjoy its sweetness.", "text": "grab_Peach", "score": "1.4340373"}, {"id": "116", "title": "Could you come to either the bar or the first table?", "text": "RobotNear_Bar | RobotNear_Table1", "score": "1.4098368"}, {"id": "80", "title": "Put the dirty napkins in the laundry box before they pile up.", "text": "put_Napkin_Box", "score": "1.3033117"}]}
{"id": 32, "question": "I'd like natural fruit juice served at the third table, or alternatively, could you switch on the air conditioner?", "answer": "On_NFCJuice_Table3 | Active_AC", "ctxs": [{"id": "75", "title": "Pour yourself a glass of wine from the bottle on the table.", "text": "drink_Wine", "score": "1.5850477"}, {"id": "59", "title": "After breakfast, put the Bread in the Bread box to keep it fresh.", "text": "put_Bread_Box", "score": "1.5850477"}, {"id": "43", "title": "After washing your hands, touch the PaperTowel to dry off.", "text": "touch_PaperTowel", "score": "1.5850477"}]}
{"id": 0, "question": "Please prepare some coffee.", "answer": "Exists_Coffee", "ctxs": [{"id": "96", "title": "Turn on the wall lamp to create a cozy atmosphere in the room.", "text": "switchon_Wall_lamp", "score": "1.4392161"}, {"id": "15", "title": "Put the leftover chips in the cabinet to keep them fresh.", "text": "put_Chips_Cabinet", "score": "1.411994"}, {"id": "76", "title": "Take a peach from the fruit bowl and enjoy a healthy snack.", "text": "grab_Peach", "score": "1.4074931"}]}
{"id": 1, "question": "Would you mind fetching my vacuum cup to the hydration area?", "answer": "On_VacuumCup_WaterStation", "ctxs": [{"id": "0", "title": "Can you walk towards the wall phone and answer it?", "text": "walktowards_Wall_phone", "score": "1.4436321"}]}
{"id": 2, "question": "Can I have some water served at the first table, please?", "answer": "On_Water_Table1", "ctxs": [{"id": "116", "title": "Could you come to either the bar or the first table?", "text": "RobotNear_Bar | RobotNear_Table1", "score": "1.6330396"}, {"id": "104", "title": "Take a peach from the fruit basket and enjoy its sweetness.", "text": "grab_Peach", "score": "1.6243432"}, {"id": "117", "title": "Please proceed to the coffee area or the first table.", "text": "RobotNear_CoffeeStation | RobotNear_Table1", "score": "1.5896306"}]}
{"id": 3, "question": "Would it be possible to send some yoghurt over to the second table?", "answer": "On_Yogurt_Table2", "ctxs": [{"id": "104", "title": "Take a peach from the fruit basket and enjoy its sweetness.", "text": "grab_Peach", "score": "1.5712897"}, {"id": "99", "title": "Put the salad bowl back in the fridge to keep it fresh.", "text": "put_Salad_Fridge", "score": "1.5189347"}, {"id": "116", "title": "Could you come to either the bar or the first table?", "text": "RobotNear_Bar | RobotNear_Table1", "score": "1.5110309"}]}
{"id": 4, "question": "Would you mind turning on the air conditioning?", "answer": "Active_AC", "ctxs": [{"id": "115", "title": "Open the curtains and the air conditioning.", "text": "Activate_Curtain & Activate_AC", "score": "1.3465716"}, {"id": "114", "title": "Close the curtains and the air conditioning.", "text": "Closed_Curtain & Closed_AC", "score": "1.3123258"}]}
{"id": 5, "question": "I'd appreciate it if you could deliver a bottled drink to the third table.", "answer": "On_BottledDrink_Table3", "ctxs": [{"id": "98", "title": "Reach for the apple on the counter and take a bite.", "text": "grab_Apple", "score": "2.0485814"}, {"id": "19", "title": "Sit at the coffee table and enjoy your coffee.", "text": "sit_Coffee_table", "score": "1.8702333"}, {"id": "99", "title": "Put the salad bowl back in the fridge to keep it fresh.", "text": "put_Salad_Fridge", "score": "1.7781181"}]}
{"id": 6, "question": "I would like a dessert at the bar, please.", "answer": "On_Dessert_Bar", "ctxs": [{"id": "31", "title": "Put the BellPepper in the fridge after cutting it.", "text": "put_BellPepper_Fridge", "score": "1.5945182"}, {"id": "107", "title": "Enjoy a glass of beer from the fridge after a long day.", "text": "drink_Beer", "score": "1.5255978"}, {"id": "73", "title": "Could you grab a papertowel and wipe the spilled milk on the counter?", "text": "grab_PaperTowel", "score": "1.4230142"}]}
{"id": 7, "question": "Could you serve crisps at Table 3?", "answer": "On_Chips_Table3", "ctxs": [{"id": "23", "title": "Touch the photo frame on the wall to straighten it.", "text": "touch_PhotoFrame", "score": "1.4765824"}, {"id": "42", "title": "Before bed, make sure to switchoff the bedside wall Lamp.", "text": "switchoff_Wall_Lamp", "score": "1.3798562"}, {"id": "8", "title": "Put the dirty dish bowl in the dishwasher after dinner.", "text": "put_Dish_bowl_Dishwasher", "score": "1.3605602"}]}
{"id": 8, "question": "Could you turn on the tube light, please?", "answer": "Active_TubeLight", "ctxs": [{"id": "100", "title": "Touch the vase on the shelf and admire its design.", "text": "touch_Vase", "score": "1.671679"}, {"id": "103", "title": "Sit on the sofa and relax while watching your favorite TV show.", "text": "sit_Sofa", "score": "1.6598958"}, {"id": "102", "title": "Switch off the lights before leaving the room to save energy.", "text": "switchoff_LightSwitch", "score": "1.6329421"}]}
{"id": 9, "question": "Could you close the curtains, please? ", "answer": "Closed_Curtain", "ctxs": [{"id": "114", "title": "Close the curtains and the air conditioning.", "text": "Closed_Curtain & Closed_AC", "score": "1.6397626"}, {"id": "115", "title": "Open the curtains and the air conditioning.", "text": "Activate_Curtain & Activate_AC", "score": "1.4493463"}, {"id": "34", "title": "Grab a WineGlass before pouring yourself a glass of wine.", "text": "grab_WineGlass", "score": "1.440821"}]}
{"id": 10, "question": "Can you make sure that table 1 is clean?", "answer": "IsClean_Table1", "ctxs": [{"id": "97", "title": "Enjoy a glass of wine from the wine bottle on the shelf.", "text": "drink_Wine", "score": "1.2857105"}, {"id": "79", "title": "Look at the beautiful wall picture frame and appreciate the artwork.", "text": "lookat_WallPictureFrame", "score": "1.2692988"}]}
{"id": 11, "question": "Please place the Bernachon on window table 6.", "answer": "On_Bernachon_WindowTable6", "ctxs": []}
{"id": 12, "question": "Please bring a milk drink to bar 2.", "answer": "On_MilkDrink_Bar2", "ctxs": [{"id": "25", "title": "Sit at the nightstand and read a book before sleeping.", "text": "sit_Nightstand", "score": "1.6117178"}, {"id": "73", "title": "Could you grab a papertowel and wipe the spilled milk on the counter?", "text": "grab_PaperTowel", "score": "1.5549135"}, {"id": "31", "title": "Put the BellPepper in the fridge after cutting it.", "text": "put_BellPepper_Fridge", "score": "1.5216745"}]}
{"id": 13, "question": "Please ensure the air conditioning is activated.", "answer": "Active_AC", "ctxs": [{"id": "115", "title": "Open the curtains and the air conditioning.", "text": "Activate_Curtain & Activate_AC", "score": "1.3816497"}, {"id": "5", "title": "Let's put the cutting board away in the cabinet.", "text": "put_Cutting_board_Cabinet", "score": "1.3112259"}, {"id": "13", "title": "Before leaving, make sure to turn off the light switch.", "text": "switchoff_LightSwitch", "score": "1.3108361"}]}
{"id": 14, "question": "Could you please check if the hall light is on?", "answer": "Active_HallLight", "ctxs": [{"id": "100", "title": "Touch the vase on the shelf and admire its design.", "text": "touch_Vase", "score": "1.5535635"}, {"id": "103", "title": "Sit on the sofa and relax while watching your favorite TV show.", "text": "sit_Sofa", "score": "1.5177954"}, {"id": "102", "title": "Switch off the lights before leaving the room to save energy.", "text": "switchoff_LightSwitch", "score": "1.501746"}]}
{"id": 15, "question": "Could you place the NFC juice on Table 2?", "answer": "On_NFCJuice_Table2", "ctxs": [{"id": "51", "title": "Switch on the Wall_lamp to brighten up the room.", "text": "switchon_Wall_lamp", "score": "1.2492551"}, {"id": "38", "title": "Put the Dish_bowl in the microwave to heat up your meal.", "text": "putin_Dish_bowl_Microwave", "score": "1.245214"}]}
{"id": 16, "question": "I'd like some spring water at Table 1.", "answer": "On_SpringWater_Table1", "ctxs": []}
{"id": 17, "question": "Please make sure the floor is clean.", "answer": "IsClean_Floor", "ctxs": [{"id": "113", "title": "Higher the heating and clean the floor please.", "text": "High_ACTemperature & IsClean_Floor", "score": "1.5170162"}, {"id": "110", "title": "Lower the heating and clean the floor please.", "text": "Low_ACTemperature & IsClean_Floor", "score": "1.4804108"}, {"id": "112", "title": "Turn up the temperature and clean the floor.", "text": "High_ACTemperature & IsClean_Floor", "score": "1.3935691"}]}
{"id": 18, "question": "Can you check if the chairs are clean?", "answer": "IsClean_Chairs", "ctxs": [{"id": "79", "title": "Look at the beautiful wall picture frame and appreciate the artwork.", "text": "lookat_WallPictureFrame", "score": "1.7996268"}, {"id": "11", "title": "Grab a peach and enjoy the sweet taste.", "text": "grab_Peach", "score": "1.5951228"}, {"id": "95", "title": "Before starting dinner, grab a plate from the cupboard.", "text": "grab_Plate", "score": "1.5029423"}]}
{"id": 19, "question": "Could you lower the air conditioning temperature?", "answer": "Low_ACTemperature", "ctxs": [{"id": "2", "title": "As you walk in, please grab a towel to wipe the table.", "text": "grab_PaperTowel", "score": "1.3800206"}, {"id": "114", "title": "Close the curtains and the air conditioning.", "text": "Closed_Curtain & Closed_AC", "score": "1.3333571"}, {"id": "110", "title": "Lower the heating and clean the floor please.", "text": "Low_ACTemperature & IsClean_Floor", "score": "1.2750804"}]}
{"id": 20, "question": "I need ADMilk at the coffee station.", "answer": "On_ADMilk_CoffeeStation", "ctxs": []}
{"id": 21, "question": "Can you bring milk to the bar?", "answer": "On_Milk_Bar", "ctxs": [{"id": "73", "title": "Could you grab a papertowel and wipe the spilled milk on the counter?", "text": "grab_PaperTowel", "score": "1.5079737"}, {"id": "104", "title": "Take a peach from the fruit basket and enjoy its sweetness.", "text": "grab_Peach", "score": "1.3949033"}, {"id": "37", "title": "Touch the PhotoFrame gently to see if it's dusty.", "text": "touch_PhotoFrame", "score": "1.3829302"}]}
{"id": 22, "question": "Please close the curtains.", "answer": "Closed_Curtain", "ctxs": [{"id": "114", "title": "Close the curtains and the air conditioning.", "text": "Closed_Curtain & Closed_AC", "score": "1.7010164"}, {"id": "34", "title": "Grab a WineGlass before pouring yourself a glass of wine.", "text": "grab_WineGlass", "score": "1.615385"}, {"id": "61", "title": "Put the Dish_bowl in the Box for storage.", "text": "put_Dish_bowl_Box", "score": "1.5509461"}]}
{"id": 23, "question": "Could you turn on the tube light?", "answer": "Active_TubeLight", "ctxs": [{"id": "100", "title": "Touch the vase on the shelf and admire its design.", "text": "touch_Vase", "score": "1.7618054"}, {"id": "103", "title": "Sit on the sofa and relax while watching your favorite TV show.", "text": "sit_Sofa", "score": "1.7068758"}, {"id": "102", "title": "Switch off the lights before leaving the room to save energy.", "text": "switchoff_LightSwitch", "score": "1.6722097"}]}
{"id": 24, "question": "Please serve a soft drink at Table 3.", "answer": "On_Softdrink_Table3", "ctxs": [{"id": "34", "title": "Grab a WineGlass before pouring yourself a glass of wine.", "text": "grab_WineGlass", "score": "1.9699062"}, {"id": "12", "title": "Switch off the TV when you're done watching.", "text": "switchoff_WallTV", "score": "1.8339455"}, {"id": "24", "title": "Put the wine glasses back in the cabinet after the party.", "text": "put_WineGlass_Cabinet", "score": "1.8013837"}]}
{"id": 25, "question": "Could you make sure the chairs are clean?", "answer": "IsClean_Chairs", "ctxs": [{"id": "79", "title": "Look at the beautiful wall picture frame and appreciate the artwork.", "text": "lookat_WallPictureFrame", "score": "1.6686699"}, {"id": "11", "title": "Grab a peach and enjoy the sweet taste.", "text": "grab_Peach", "score": "1.6139277"}, {"id": "95", "title": "Before starting dinner, grab a plate from the cupboard.", "text": "grab_Plate", "score": "1.5798091"}]}
{"id": 26, "question": "I'd like a dessert at the bar, please.", "answer": "On_Dessert_Bar", "ctxs": [{"id": "31", "title": "Put the BellPepper in the fridge after cutting it.", "text": "put_BellPepper_Fridge", "score": "1.5722303"}, {"id": "107", "title": "Enjoy a glass of beer from the fridge after a long day.", "text": "drink_Beer", "score": "1.5279562"}, {"id": "73", "title": "Could you grab a papertowel and wipe the spilled milk on the counter?", "text": "grab_PaperTowel", "score": "1.3950078"}]}
{"id": 27, "question": "It's quite toasty inside, could you please lower the air conditioning temperature?", "answer": "Low_ACTemperature", "ctxs": [{"id": "114", "title": "Close the curtains and the air conditioning.", "text": "Closed_Curtain & Closed_AC", "score": "1.3132653"}, {"id": "2", "title": "As you walk in, please grab a towel to wipe the table.", "text": "grab_PaperTowel", "score": "1.2971277"}, {"id": "64", "title": "After dinner, put the Bottle_water back in the fridge.", "text": "put_Bottle_water_Fridge", "score": "1.289201"}]}
{"id": 28, "question": "Could you convey some coffee to the table six?", "answer": "On_Coffee_WindowTable6", "ctxs": [{"id": "32", "title": "Sit on the Chair and relax for a while.", "text": "sit_Chair", "score": "1.51617"}, {"id": "23", "title": "Touch the photo frame on the wall to straighten it.", "text": "touch_PhotoFrame", "score": "1.4974487"}, {"id": "15", "title": "Put the leftover chips in the cabinet to keep them fresh.", "text": "put_Chips_Cabinet", "score": "1.40658"}]}
{"id": 29, "question": "I'd like a glass of water at Bar 2.", "answer": "On_Water_Bar2", "ctxs": [{"id": "98", "title": "Reach for the apple on the counter and take a bite.", "text": "grab_Apple", "score": "1.2633426"}, {"id": "73", "title": "Could you grab a papertowel and wipe the spilled milk on the counter?", "text": "grab_PaperTowel", "score": "1.2490562"}]}
{"id": 0, "question": "Can you walk towards the kitchen table and sit on the sofa?", "answer": "walktowards_Kitchentable & sit_Sofa", "ctxs": [{"id": "20", "title": "Walk towards the kitchen table and sit on the sofa.", "text": "walktowards_Kitchentable & sit_Sofa", "score": "1.9858881"}, {"id": "0", "title": "Walk towards the kitchen table and sit on the sofa.", "text": "walktowards_Kitchentable & sit_Sofa", "score": "1.9858881"}, {"id": "61", "title": "Walk towards the sofa and sit down with a plate of salad.", "text": "walktowards_Sofa & sit_Plate", "score": "1.5912002"}]}
{"id": 1, "question": "Please turn left and grab a bottle of wine from the fridge.", "answer": "turn_left & grab_Bottlewater", "ctxs": [{"id": "1", "title": "Turn left and grab a bottle of wine from the fridge.", "text": "turn_left & grab_Bottlewater", "score": "2.0387535"}, {"id": "42", "title": "Turn left and open the Fridge to get a bottle of water.", "text": "turn_left & open_Fridge", "score": "1.5850983"}, {"id": "21", "title": "Turn left and grab an apple from the fridge.", "text": "turn_left & grab_Apple", "score": "1.5189935"}]}
{"id": 2, "question": "Switch off the ceiling fan and the ceiling lamp before leaving the room, please.", "answer": "switchoff_CeilingFan | switchoff_Ceilinglamp", "ctxs": [{"id": "2", "title": "Please switch off the ceiling fan and the ceiling lamp before leaving the room.", "text": "switchoff_CeilingFan | switchoff_Ceilinglamp", "score": "2.3717394"}, {"id": "94", "title": "Touch the ceiling fan and switch it off before leaving the room.", "text": "touch_CeilingFan & switchoff_CeilingFan", "score": "2.1021717"}, {"id": "84", "title": "Turn right and switch off the Ceiling lamp before leaving the room.", "text": "turn_right & switchoff_Ceilinglamp", "score": "2.069967"}]}
{"id": 3, "question": "Could you please walk towards the dining table and look at the wall phone.", "answer": "walktowards_DiningTable & lookat_Wallphone", "ctxs": [{"id": "3", "title": "Walk towards the dining table and look at the wall phone.", "text": "walktowards_DiningTable & lookat_Wallphone", "score": "2.332223"}, {"id": "85", "title": "Walk towards the Wall phone and touch it to answer the call.", "text": "walktowards_Wallphone & touch_Wallphone", "score": "1.8424162"}, {"id": "14", "title": "Walk towards the wall picture frame and look at the wall TV.", "text": "walktowards_WallPictureFrame & lookat_WallTV", "score": "1.605407"}]}
{"id": 4, "question": "Remember to close the fridge before bedtime.", "answer": "close_Fridge", "ctxs": [{"id": "4", "title": "Before bedtime, remember to close the fridge and the cabinet.", "text": "close_Fridge | close_Cabinet", "score": "2.145586"}, {"id": "12", "title": "Touch the fridge and turn off the toaster before leaving the kitchen.", "text": "touch_Fridge & switchoff_Toaster", "score": "1.5486676"}, {"id": "28", "title": "Before going out, make sure to close the drawer and shut down the washing machine.", "text": "close_Drawer | switchoff_Washingmachine", "score": "1.4814725"}]}
{"id": 5, "question": "Grab the chef knife and put it on the cutting board, please.", "answer": "grab_ChefKnife & put_ChefKnife_Cuttingboard", "ctxs": [{"id": "5", "title": "Grab the chef knife and put it on the cutting board.", "text": "grab_ChefKnife & put_ChefKnife_Cuttingboard", "score": "2.111263"}, {"id": "24", "title": "Can you grab the chef knife but do not put it in the dish bowl?", "text": "grab_ChefKnife & ~put_ChefKnife_Dishbowl", "score": "1.715181"}, {"id": "75", "title": "Sit on the Chair and grab a Chef Knife from the Shelf.", "text": "sit_Chair & grab_ChefKnife", "score": "1.7033324"}]}
{"id": 6, "question": "Open the drawer and put the spoon in it, thank you.", "answer": "open_Drawer & put_Spoon_Drawer", "ctxs": [{"id": "6", "title": "Open the drawer and put the spoon in it.", "text": "open_Drawer & put_Spoon_Drawer", "score": "1.9509706"}, {"id": "44", "title": "Grab a spoon and put it on the kitchen table.", "text": "grab_Spoon & put_Spoon_Kitchentable", "score": "1.5538282"}, {"id": "45", "title": "Turn right and open the drawer to get a napkin.", "text": "turn_right & open_Drawer", "score": "1.4348979"}]}
{"id": 7, "question": "Switch on the stove and turn right to walk towards the shelf.", "answer": "switchon_Stove & walktowards_Shelf", "ctxs": [{"id": "7", "title": "Switch on the stove and turn right to walk towards the shelf.", "text": "switchon_Stove & walktowards_Shelf", "score": "2.1969965"}, {"id": "30", "title": "Walk towards the stove and switch on the kettle.", "text": "walktowards_Stove & switchon_Kettle", "score": "1.7335224"}, {"id": "29", "title": "Turn left and grab a bottle of water, then walk towards the shelf.", "text": "turn_left & grab_Bottlewater | walktowards_Shelf", "score": "1.6646931"}]}
{"id": 8, "question": "Hellp, please sit on the chair and open the microwave to heat the bread slice.", "answer": "sit_Chair & open_Microwave", "ctxs": [{"id": "8", "title": "Sit on the chair and open the microwave to heat the bread slice.", "text": "sit_Chair & open_Microwave", "score": "2.2222743"}, {"id": "52", "title": "Turn right and open the microwave to warm up the bread slice.", "text": "turn_right & open_Microwave", "score": "1.9872141"}, {"id": "47", "title": "Walk towards the microwave and switch it on to heat up the leftovers.", "text": "walktowards_Microwave & switchon_Microwave", "score": "1.5295179"}]}
{"id": 9, "question": "Walk towards the nightstand and touch the wall lamp.", "answer": "walktowards_Nightstand & touch_Walllamp", "ctxs": [{"id": "22", "title": "Walk towards the nightstand and touch the wall lamp.", "text": "walktowards_Nightstand & touch_Walllamp", "score": "2.254407"}, {"id": "9", "title": "Walk towards the nightstand and touch the wall lamp.", "text": "walktowards_Nightstand & touch_Walllamp", "score": "2.254407"}, {"id": "100", "title": "Walk towards the curtains and touch the ceiling lamp.", "text": "walktowards_Curtains & touch_Ceilinglamp", "score": "1.8568485"}]}
{"id": 10, "question": "Turn left and I want to drink a mug of milk.", "answer": "turn_left & drink_Milk", "ctxs": [{"id": "10", "title": "Turn left and drink a mug of milk.", "text": "turn_left & drink_Milk", "score": "2.0258646"}, {"id": "32", "title": "Grab a spoon and drink some milk from the mug.", "text": "grab_Spoon & drink_Milk", "score": "1.5254202"}, {"id": "103", "title": "Pour yourself a mug of milk and relax on the sofa.", "text": "drink_Milk | sit_Sofa", "score": "1.3011961"}]}
{"id": 11, "question": "I want you to grab the banana but do not put it in the dish bowl.", "answer": "grab_Banana & ~put_Apple_Dishbowl", "ctxs": [{"id": "11", "title": "Grab the apple but do not put it in the dish bowl.", "text": "grab_Apple & ~put_Apple_Dishbowl", "score": "1.8483577"}, {"id": "68", "title": "Grab the Tomato but do not put it in the Dish bowl.", "text": "grab_Tomato & ~put_Tomato_Dishbowl", "score": "1.7429965"}, {"id": "24", "title": "Can you grab the chef knife but do not put it in the dish bowl?", "text": "grab_ChefKnife & ~put_ChefKnife_Dishbowl", "score": "1.5903908"}]}
{"id": 12, "question": "Now, touch the fridge and turn off the toaster before leaving the kitchen.", "answer": "touch_Fridge & switchoff_Toaster", "ctxs": [{"id": "12", "title": "Touch the fridge and turn off the toaster before leaving the kitchen.", "text": "touch_Fridge & switchoff_Toaster", "score": "2.2338438"}, {"id": "79", "title": "Walk towards the Microwave and switch it off before leaving the Kitchen.", "text": "walktowards_Microwave & switchoff_Microwave", "score": "1.7765355"}, {"id": "104", "title": "Turn right and touch the toaster to switch it off.", "text": "turn_right & switchoff_Toaster", "score": "1.7438774"}]}
{"id": 13, "question": "Can you put the carrot in the dish bowl and switch off the oven tray?", "answer": "put_Carrot_Dishbowl & switchoff_OvenTray", "ctxs": [{"id": "13", "title": "Put the carrot in the dish bowl and switch on the oven tray.", "text": "put_Carrot_Dishbowl & switchon_OvenTray", "score": "1.9124275"}, {"id": "50", "title": "Walk towards the oven tray and switchoff the oven after baking.", "text": "walktowards_OvenTray & switchoff_Stove", "score": "1.4553632"}, {"id": "11", "title": "Grab the apple but do not put it in the dish bowl.", "text": "grab_Apple & ~put_Apple_Dishbowl", "score": "1.3032111"}]}
{"id": 14, "question": "Walk towards the sofa frame and look at the wall TV.", "answer": "walktowards_Sofa & lookat_WallTV", "ctxs": [{"id": "14", "title": "Walk towards the wall picture frame and look at the wall TV.", "text": "walktowards_WallPictureFrame & lookat_WallTV", "score": "1.9727267"}, {"id": "97", "title": "Walk towards the wall picture frame and touch the wall TV.", "text": "walktowards_WallPictureFrame & touch_WallTV", "score": "1.8787608"}, {"id": "41", "title": "Sit on the sofa and look at the WallTV for entertainment.", "text": "sit_Sofa & lookat_WallTV", "score": "1.7841482"}]}
{"id": 15, "question": "Before leaving the room, remember to turn off the dishwasher and the washing machine.", "answer": "switchoff_Dishwasher | switchoff_Washingmachine", "ctxs": [{"id": "15", "title": "Before leaving the room, make sure to turn off the dishwasher and the washing machine.", "text": "switchoff_Dishwasher | switchoff_Washingmachine", "score": "2.2087355"}, {"id": "28", "title": "Before going out, make sure to close the drawer and shut down the washing machine.", "text": "close_Drawer | switchoff_Washingmachine", "score": "1.8236275"}, {"id": "73", "title": "Before leaving the room, ensure to close the Door and switch off the LightSwitch.", "text": "close_Door & switchoff_LightSwitch", "score": "1.7111539"}]}
{"id": 16, "question": "Grab the bread and sit on the sofa now.", "answer": "grab_Bread & sit_Sofa", "ctxs": [{"id": "16", "title": "Grab the bread and sit on the sofa to eat it.", "text": "grab_Bread & sit_Sofa", "score": "2.154438"}, {"id": "20", "title": "Walk towards the kitchen table and sit on the sofa.", "text": "walktowards_Kitchentable & sit_Sofa", "score": "1.6974733"}, {"id": "0", "title": "Walk towards the kitchen table and sit on the sofa.", "text": "walktowards_Kitchentable & sit_Sofa", "score": "1.6974733"}]}
{"id": 17, "question": "Please ppen the fridge for me.", "answer": "open_Fridge", "ctxs": []}
{"id": 18, "question": "Turn right and grab the frying pan for cooking.", "answer": "turn_right & grab_FryingPan", "ctxs": [{"id": "18", "title": "Turn right and grab the frying pan for cooking.", "text": "turn_right & grab_FryingPan", "score": "2.11728"}, {"id": "57", "title": "Turn right and grab the cutting board for preparing dinner.", "text": "turn_right & grab_Cuttingboard", "score": "1.5803828"}, {"id": "92", "title": "Turn right and sit at the dining table for dinner.", "text": "turn_right & sit_DiningTable", "score": "1.4591947"}]}
{"id": 19, "question": "Sit at the sofa and switch on the kettle to make coffee.", "answer": "sit_Sofa & switchon_Kettle", "ctxs": [{"id": "19", "title": "Sit at the desk and switch on the kettle to make coffee.", "text": "sit_Desk & switchon_Kettle", "score": "2.0377872"}, {"id": "30", "title": "Walk towards the stove and switch on the kettle.", "text": "walktowards_Stove & switchon_Kettle", "score": "1.6141841"}, {"id": "88", "title": "Sit on the sofa and touch the wall lamp to turn it on.", "text": "sit_Sofa & switchon_Walllamp", "score": "1.5747557"}]}
{"id": 20, "question": "Walk towards the kitchen table and sit on the sofa.", "answer": "walktowards_Kitchentable & sit_Sofa", "ctxs": [{"id": "20", "title": "Walk towards the kitchen table and sit on the sofa.", "text": "walktowards_Kitchentable & sit_Sofa", "score": "2.3034098"}, {"id": "0", "title": "Walk towards the kitchen table and sit on the sofa.", "text": "walktowards_Kitchentable & sit_Sofa", "score": "2.3034098"}, {"id": "61", "title": "Walk towards the sofa and sit down with a plate of salad.", "text": "walktowards_Sofa & sit_Plate", "score": "1.8541837"}]}
{"id": 21, "question": "Turn right and grab an apple from the fridge.", "answer": "turn_right & grab_Apple", "ctxs": [{"id": "21", "title": "Turn left and grab an apple from the fridge.", "text": "turn_left & grab_Apple", "score": "2.1138492"}, {"id": "38", "title": "Walk towards the fridge and grab a peach.", "text": "walktowards_Fridge & grab_Peach", "score": "1.5245647"}, {"id": "1", "title": "Turn left and grab a bottle of wine from the fridge.", "text": "turn_left & grab_Bottlewater", "score": "1.5224482"}]}
{"id": 22, "question": "Walk towards the nightstand and touch the chair.", "answer": "walktowards_Nightstand & touch_Chair", "ctxs": [{"id": "22", "title": "Walk towards the nightstand and touch the wall lamp.", "text": "walktowards_Nightstand & touch_Walllamp", "score": "1.901144"}, {"id": "9", "title": "Walk towards the nightstand and touch the wall lamp.", "text": "walktowards_Nightstand & touch_Walllamp", "score": "1.901144"}, {"id": "93", "title": "Walk towards the nightstand and put the napkin in the drawer.", "text": "walktowards_Nightstand & put_Napkin_Drawer", "score": "1.706887"}]}
{"id": 23, "question": "Before you leave the living room, ensure to turn off the ceiling fan and the ceiling lamp.", "answer": "switchoff_CeilingFan | switchoff_Ceilinglamp", "ctxs": [{"id": "23", "title": "Before you leave the living room, ensure to turn off the ceiling fan and the ceiling lamp.", "text": "switchoff_CeilingFan | switchoff_Ceilinglamp", "score": "2.32673"}, {"id": "94", "title": "Touch the ceiling fan and switch it off before leaving the room.", "text": "touch_CeilingFan & switchoff_CeilingFan", "score": "1.9963164"}, {"id": "2", "title": "Please switch off the ceiling fan and the ceiling lamp before leaving the room.", "text": "switchoff_CeilingFan | switchoff_Ceilinglamp", "score": "1.9852476"}]}
{"id": 24, "question": "Can you grab the chef knife but do not put it in the dish bowl?", "answer": "grab_ChefKnife & ~put_ChefKnife_Dishbowl", "ctxs": [{"id": "24", "title": "Can you grab the chef knife but do not put it in the dish bowl?", "text": "grab_ChefKnife & ~put_ChefKnife_Dishbowl", "score": "2.2908554"}, {"id": "11", "title": "Grab the apple but do not put it in the dish bowl.", "text": "grab_Apple & ~put_Apple_Dishbowl", "score": "1.6979226"}, {"id": "5", "title": "Grab the chef knife and put it on the cutting board.", "text": "grab_ChefKnife & put_ChefKnife_Cuttingboard", "score": "1.6672258"}]}
{"id": 25, "question": "I wang you to turn right and sit on the nightstand for a moment.", "answer": "turn_right & sit_Nightstand", "ctxs": [{"id": "25", "title": "Turn right and sit on the nightstand for a moment.", "text": "turn_right & sit_Nightstand", "score": "2.224915"}, {"id": "33", "title": "Turn right and sit on the dining table to have breakfast.", "text": "turn_right & sit_DiningTable", "score": "1.6148686"}, {"id": "22", "title": "Walk towards the nightstand and touch the wall lamp.", "text": "walktowards_Nightstand & touch_Walllamp", "score": "1.5384597"}]}
{"id": 26, "question": "I need you to walk towards the curtains and open the fridge.", "answer": "walktowards_Curtains & open_Fridge", "ctxs": [{"id": "26", "title": "Walk towards the curtains and open the fridge.", "text": "walktowards_Curtains & open_Fridge", "score": "2.0723326"}, {"id": "79", "title": "Walk towards the Microwave and switch it off before leaving the Kitchen.", "text": "walktowards_Microwave & switchoff_Microwave", "score": "1.5632608"}, {"id": "100", "title": "Walk towards the curtains and touch the ceiling lamp.", "text": "walktowards_Curtains & touch_Ceilinglamp", "score": "1.5331001"}]}
{"id": 27, "question": "Please switch on the microwave and put the chicken in the frying pan.", "answer": "switchon_Microwave & put_Chicken_FryingPan", "ctxs": [{"id": "27", "title": "Switch on the microwave and put the chicken in the frying pan.", "text": "switchon_Microwave & put_Chicken_FryingPan", "score": "1.8956397"}, {"id": "47", "title": "Walk towards the microwave and switch it on to heat up the leftovers.", "text": "walktowards_Microwave & switchon_Microwave", "score": "1.2697564"}, {"id": "36", "title": "Grab a plate and put the pancake on the kitchen table.", "text": "grab_Plate & put_Pancake_Kitchentable", "score": "1.2430472"}]}
{"id": 0, "question": "Please grab a potato and put it in the microwave.", "answer": "grab_Potato & putin_Potato_Microwave", "ctxs": [{"id": "174", "title": "Please grab a bread slice and place it in the microwave.", "text": "grab_Breadslice & putin_Breadslice_Microwave", "score": "1.6674521"}, {"id": "56", "title": "Let's put the bread slices in the microwave for a quick snack.", "text": "putin_Breadslice_Microwave", "score": "1.4786623"}, {"id": "6", "title": "Let's put the bread slices in the microwave for breakfast.", "text": "putin_Breadslice_Microwave", "score": "1.4178183"}]}
{"id": 1, "question": "Check if the cabinet is open or the fridge is closed.", "answer": "open_Cabinet | close_Fridge", "ctxs": [{"id": "177", "title": "Check if the cabinet is closed and the wall TV is switched on.", "text": "close_Cabinet & switchon_WallTV", "score": "1.8245955"}, {"id": "141", "title": "Check if the fridge door is closed, then switch on the light switch in the kitchen.", "text": "close_Fridge & switchon_LightSwitch", "score": "1.8084135"}, {"id": "102", "title": "Check if the fridge door is closed and switch on the ceiling fan.", "text": "close_Fridge & switchon_CeilingFan", "score": "1.7325896"}]}
{"id": 2, "question": "Sit on the chair and drink some milk.", "answer": "sit_Chair & drink_Milk", "ctxs": [{"id": "165", "title": "Confirm if the microwave is closed and drink a glass of milk.", "text": "close_Microwave & drink_Milk", "score": "1.4042847"}, {"id": "117", "title": "Sit on the chair and touch the shelf.", "text": "sit_Chair & touch_Shelf", "score": "1.3953022"}, {"id": "89", "title": "How about having a sip of milk before bed?", "text": "drink_Milk", "score": "1.3566194"}]}
{"id": 3, "question": "Turn left and walk towards the ceiling lamp.", "answer": "turn_left & walktowards_Ceilinglamp", "ctxs": [{"id": "58", "title": "Touch the wall to turn on the ceiling lamp.", "text": "touch_Ceilinglamp", "score": "1.7625399"}, {"id": "28", "title": "Touch the ceiling lamp to adjust the brightness in the room.", "text": "touch_Ceilinglamp", "score": "1.5610961"}, {"id": "18", "title": "Touch the wall lamp to adjust the lighting in the room.", "text": "touch_Walllamp", "score": "1.5055977"}]}
{"id": 4, "question": "If the stove is on, switch it off immediately.", "answer": "lookat_Stove & switchoff_Stove", "ctxs": [{"id": "112", "title": "If the stove is on, turn it off, or unplug the kettle.", "text": "switchoff_Stove | switchoff_Kettle", "score": "1.7689048"}, {"id": "182", "title": "Check if the stove is off before turning on the kettle.", "text": "switchoff_Stove & switchon_Kettle", "score": "1.7522017"}, {"id": "156", "title": "Check if the stove is off before turning on the microwave.", "text": "~switchoff_Stove & switchon_Microwave", "score": "1.6895155"}]}
{"id": 5, "question": "Open the curtains and look at the wall picture frame.", "answer": "open_Curtains & lookat_Wallpictureframe", "ctxs": [{"id": "104", "title": "Sit on the sofa and touch the wall lamp.", "text": "sit_Sofa & touch_Walllamp", "score": "1.39414"}, {"id": "98", "title": "Touch the curtains to open them and let in some sunlight.", "text": "touch_Curtains", "score": "1.3867731"}, {"id": "138", "title": "If the wall lamp is off, switch it on; otherwise, touch the curtains.", "text": "switchoff_Walllamp | touch_Curtains", "score": "1.3646647"}]}
{"id": 6, "question": "Put the wine glass in the dishwasher after use.", "answer": "putin_WineGlass_Dishwasher", "ctxs": [{"id": "199", "title": "If the wine glass is dirty, wash it; otherwise, put it in the sink.", "text": "lookat_WineGlass | putin_WineGlass_Fridge", "score": "1.7526274"}, {"id": "26", "title": "Let's put the dirty plates in the dishwasher after dinner.", "text": "put_Plate_Dishwasher", "score": "1.5114472"}, {"id": "166", "title": "Please grab a wine glass and put it in the fridge.", "text": "grab_WineGlass & putin_WineGlass_Fridge", "score": "1.4841561"}]}
{"id": 7, "question": "Ensure the toaster is off and the kettle is unplugged.", "answer": "switchoff_Toaster & switchoff_Kettle", "ctxs": [{"id": "147", "title": "Make sure the kettle is unplugged and the toaster is switched off before you leave.", "text": "switchoff_Kettle & switchoff_Toaster", "score": "2.0705752"}, {"id": "139", "title": "Ensure the kettle is unplugged before switching off the light switch.", "text": "lookat_Kettle & switchoff_LightSwitch", "score": "1.9684657"}, {"id": "112", "title": "If the stove is on, turn it off, or unplug the kettle.", "text": "switchoff_Stove | switchoff_Kettle", "score": "1.8794215"}]}
{"id": 8, "question": "Touch the wall TV before switching on the ceiling fan.", "answer": "touch_wallTV & switchon_CeilingFan", "ctxs": [{"id": "113", "title": "Touch the wall TV and switch on the wall phone.", "text": "touch_WallTV & switchon_Wallphone", "score": "1.7928013"}, {"id": "58", "title": "Touch the wall to turn on the ceiling lamp.", "text": "touch_Ceilinglamp", "score": "1.7893205"}, {"id": "179", "title": "Before you sit on the sofa, switch off the wall phone and ceiling fan.", "text": "switchoff_Wallphone & switchoff_CeilingFan", "score": "1.7891921"}]}
{"id": 9, "question": "If the dish bowl is empty, grab a spoon from the drawer.", "answer": "lookat_Dishbowl & grab_Spoon", "ctxs": [{"id": "110", "title": "Grab a spoon and put it in the dish bowl.", "text": "grab_Spoon & putin_Spoon_Dishbowl", "score": "1.7548963"}, {"id": "36", "title": "Put the clean dishes in the cabinet before they get stacked up.", "text": "putin_Plate_Cabinet", "score": "1.4950113"}, {"id": "175", "title": "If the dishwasher is open, close it, and turn on the microwave.", "text": "close_Dishwasher & switchon_Microwave", "score": "1.4406328"}]}
{"id": 10, "question": "Check if the cutting board is clean before grabbing the chef knife.", "answer": "lookat_Cuttingboard & grab_ChefKnife", "ctxs": [{"id": "193", "title": "Ensure the cutting board is clean before using the chef's knife.", "text": "lookat_Cuttingboard & grab_ChefKnife", "score": "2.0349405"}, {"id": "170", "title": "Before you start cooking, grab a chef knife and put it on the cutting board.", "text": "grab_ChefKnife & put_ChefKnife_Cuttingboard", "score": "1.8231723"}, {"id": "132", "title": "If the chef knife is on the shelf, grab it.", "text": "lookat_ChefKnife | grab_ChefKnife", "score": "1.4841206"}]}
{"id": 11, "question": "Switch on the washing machine and close its door.", "answer": "switchon_WashingMachine & close_WashingMachine", "ctxs": [{"id": "162", "title": "If the dishwasher door is open, close it; otherwise, turn on the light switch.", "text": "close_Dishwasher | switchon_LightSwitch", "score": "1.5735248"}, {"id": "148", "title": "Check if the dishwasher is closed before starting the washing machine.", "text": "close_Dishwasher & switchon_Washingmachine", "score": "1.5698493"}, {"id": "101", "title": "Turn off the light switch and close the fridge door.", "text": "switchoff_LightSwitch & close_Fridge", "score": "1.563788"}]}
{"id": 12, "question": "If the wine is not in the fridge, put it there.", "answer": "lookat_Wine | putin_Wine_Fridge", "ctxs": [{"id": "166", "title": "Please grab a wine glass and put it in the fridge.", "text": "grab_WineGlass & putin_WineGlass_Fridge", "score": "1.7628037"}, {"id": "75", "title": "Don't forget to close the fridge after taking out the wine.", "text": "close_Fridge", "score": "1.643426"}, {"id": "63", "title": "Open the fridge and check if we have any wine left.", "text": "open_Fridge", "score": "1.6175191"}]}
{"id": 13, "question": "Take a peach from the fruit basket and sit at the desk.", "answer": "grab_Peach & sit_Desk", "ctxs": [{"id": "22", "title": "Grab a peach from the fruit basket on the counter.", "text": "grab_Peach", "score": "1.70759"}, {"id": "72", "title": "Please grab a peach from the fruit basket for me.", "text": "grab_Peach", "score": "1.6168795"}, {"id": "100", "title": "Please grab a peach and place it on the shelf.", "text": "grab_Peach & put_Peach_Shelf", "score": "1.5063674"}]}
{"id": 14, "question": "Turn right and check the wall lamp.", "answer": "turn_right & lookat_Walllamp", "ctxs": [{"id": "58", "title": "Touch the wall to turn on the ceiling lamp.", "text": "touch_Ceilinglamp", "score": "1.7520132"}, {"id": "68", "title": "Touch the shelf to turn off the wall lamps.", "text": "touch_Shelf", "score": "1.63841"}, {"id": "18", "title": "Touch the wall lamp to adjust the lighting in the room.", "text": "touch_Walllamp", "score": "1.6108186"}]}
{"id": 15, "question": "If the cereal box is empty, grab a new one from the shelf.", "answer": "lookat_Box | grab_Cereal", "ctxs": [{"id": "194", "title": "Before preparing breakfast, check if the cereal box is empty or the milk carton is expired.", "text": "lookat_Cereal | lookat_Milk", "score": "1.6307163"}, {"id": "76", "title": "Put the cereal box in the kitchen cabinet for storage.", "text": "put_Cereal_Cabinet", "score": "1.5530438"}, {"id": "13", "title": "Open the kitchen cabinet to get the cereal for breakfast.", "text": "open_Cabinet", "score": "1.3930154"}]}
{"id": 16, "question": "Open the fridge and take out a bottlewater.", "answer": "open_Fridge & grab_Bottlewater", "ctxs": [{"id": "121", "title": "Check if the fridge door is open before grabbing a bottle of water.", "text": "lookat_Fridge & grab_Bottlewater", "score": "1.6063766"}, {"id": "181", "title": "Grab a bottle of water from the fridge and put it on the dining table.", "text": "grab_Bottlewater & put_Bottlewater_DiningTable", "score": "1.5906093"}, {"id": "12", "title": "Could you grab a bottle of water from the fridge, please?", "text": "grab_Bottlewater", "score": "1.4909122"}]}
{"id": 17, "question": "Close the cabinet door and switch on the kitchen table lamp.", "answer": "close_Cabinet & switchon_Walllamp", "ctxs": [{"id": "172", "title": "Close the stove and switch off the ceiling lamp.", "text": "close_Stove & switchoff_Ceilinglamp", "score": "1.6828817"}, {"id": "190", "title": "If the wall lamp is on, switch it off; otherwise, close the fridge door.", "text": "switchoff_Walllamp | close_Fridge", "score": "1.6619165"}, {"id": "101", "title": "Turn off the light switch and close the fridge door.", "text": "switchoff_LightSwitch & close_Fridge", "score": "1.6279439"}]}
{"id": 18, "question": "Please touch the dishwasher to see if it's still running.", "answer": "walktowards_Dishwasher & touch_Dishwasher", "ctxs": [{"id": "8", "title": "Touch the dishwasher to see if it's still running.", "text": "touch_Dishwasher", "score": "2.0417671"}, {"id": "148", "title": "Check if the dishwasher is closed before starting the washing machine.", "text": "close_Dishwasher & switchon_Washingmachine", "score": "1.5402868"}, {"id": "157", "title": "If the shelf is touched, switch off the dishwasher.", "text": "touch_Shelf & switchoff_Dishwasher", "score": "1.4689417"}]}
{"id": 19, "question": "Check if the dining table is clean or the sofa needs arranging.", "answer": "lookat_DiningTable | lookat_Sofa", "ctxs": [{"id": "137", "title": "Check if the chair is occupied before grabbing a bottle of wine.", "text": "touch_Chair & grab_WineGlass", "score": "1.411159"}, {"id": "195", "title": "If the napkin is dirty, grab a fresh one; otherwise, check the potato in the fridge.", "text": "lookat_Napkin | lookat_Potato", "score": "1.3294132"}, {"id": "126", "title": "Before leaving, check if the dishwasher is closed; if not, close it.", "text": "lookat_Dishwasher | close_Dishwasher", "score": "1.2899089"}]}
{"id": 20, "question": "Let's put the bread slices in the microwave for breakfast.", "answer": "open_Microwave & putin_Breadslice_Microwave", "ctxs": [{"id": "6", "title": "Let's put the bread slices in the microwave for breakfast.", "text": "putin_Breadslice_Microwave", "score": "2.3177285"}, {"id": "56", "title": "Let's put the bread slices in the microwave for a quick snack.", "text": "putin_Breadslice_Microwave", "score": "2.095482"}, {"id": "174", "title": "Please grab a bread slice and place it in the microwave.", "text": "grab_Breadslice & putin_Breadslice_Microwave", "score": "1.9050122"}]}
{"id": 21, "question": "Put the pancake on the plate and pour chocolate syrup.", "answer": "put_Pancake_Plate & grab_ChocolateSyrup", "ctxs": [{"id": "110", "title": "Grab a spoon and put it in the dish bowl.", "text": "grab_Spoon & putin_Spoon_Dishbowl", "score": "1.3501039"}, {"id": "130", "title": "Grab a bread slice and put it on the plate beside the mug.", "text": "grab_Breadslice & put_Breadslice_Plate", "score": "1.3100399"}, {"id": "146", "title": "Can you open the microwave door and put the chocolate syrup in it?", "text": "open_Microwave & putin_ChocolateSyrup_Microwave", "score": "1.3059506"}]}
{"id": 22, "question": "If the wall phone is ringing, touch it to answer.", "answer": "lookat_Wallphone & touch_Wallphone", "ctxs": [{"id": "78", "title": "Touch the wall phone to answer the incoming call.", "text": "touch_Wallphone", "score": "2.1969488"}, {"id": "113", "title": "Touch the wall TV and switch on the wall phone.", "text": "touch_WallTV & switchon_Wallphone", "score": "1.7717047"}, {"id": "58", "title": "Touch the wall to turn on the ceiling lamp.", "text": "touch_Ceilinglamp", "score": "1.4834942"}]}
{"id": 23, "question": "Take a bread slice and put it in the toaster.", "answer": "grab_Breadslice & putin_Breadslice_Toaster", "ctxs": [{"id": "119", "title": "Grab a bread slice and put it on the plate.", "text": "grab_Breadslice & put_Breadslice_Plate", "score": "1.7960786"}, {"id": "6", "title": "Let's put the bread slices in the microwave for breakfast.", "text": "putin_Breadslice_Microwave", "score": "1.7817755"}, {"id": "174", "title": "Please grab a bread slice and place it in the microwave.", "text": "grab_Breadslice & putin_Breadslice_Microwave", "score": "1.7606294"}]}
{"id": 24, "question": "Ensure the ceiling fan is off and the curtains are closed.", "answer": "switchoff_CeilingFan & close_Curtains", "ctxs": [{"id": "161", "title": "Check if the fridge is closed and switch on the ceiling fan.", "text": "close_Fridge & switchon_CeilingFan", "score": "1.8586265"}, {"id": "115", "title": "Check if the fridge door is closed and switch off the ceiling fan.", "text": "close_Fridge & switchoff_CeilingFan", "score": "1.8549507"}, {"id": "153", "title": "Make sure the ceiling fan is off and the ceiling lamp is on before you go.", "text": "switchoff_CeilingFan & switchon_Ceilinglamp", "score": "1.8363234"}]}
{"id": 25, "question": "Drink water from the glass then place it in the dishwasher.", "answer": "drink_Bottlewater & putin_WaterGlass_Dishwasher", "ctxs": [{"id": "181", "title": "Grab a bottle of water from the fridge and put it on the dining table.", "text": "grab_Bottlewater & put_Bottlewater_DiningTable", "score": "1.6509286"}, {"id": "199", "title": "If the wine glass is dirty, wash it; otherwise, put it in the sink.", "text": "lookat_WineGlass | putin_WineGlass_Fridge", "score": "1.5260468"}, {"id": "37", "title": "Don't forget to switch on the dishwasher before putting in the dishes.", "text": "switchon_Dishwasher", "score": "1.4339883"}]}
{"id": 26, "question": "If the nightstand drawer is open, close it gently.", "answer": "lookat_Drawer & close_Drawer", "ctxs": [{"id": "123", "title": "If the nightstand light is on, please turn it off; otherwise, close the microwave door.", "text": "switchoff_Ceilinglamp & close_Microwave", "score": "1.6660376"}, {"id": "88", "title": "Touch the nightstand to turn off the lamp before bed.", "text": "touch_Nightstand", "score": "1.6040998"}, {"id": "158", "title": "Before you leave, make sure the fridge is closed and the nightstand lamp is on.", "text": "close_Fridge & switchon_Nightstand", "score": "1.561574"}]}
{"id": 27, "question": "Cut the carrot on the cutting board with the chef knife.", "answer": "lookat_Cuttingboard & grab_ChefKnife", "ctxs": [{"id": "170", "title": "Before you start cooking, grab a chef knife and put it on the cutting board.", "text": "grab_ChefKnife & put_ChefKnife_Cuttingboard", "score": "1.6861166"}, {"id": "193", "title": "Ensure the cutting board is clean before using the chef's knife.", "text": "lookat_Cuttingboard & grab_ChefKnife", "score": "1.6066867"}, {"id": "160", "title": "Please grab a cutting board and place it on the kitchen table.", "text": "grab_Cuttingboard & put_Cuttingboard_Kitchentable", "score": "1.4307647"}]}
{"id": 28, "question": "Check the frying pan temperature and turn off the stove.", "answer": "touch_FryingPan & switchoff_Stove", "ctxs": [{"id": "156", "title": "Check if the stove is off before turning on the microwave.", "text": "~switchoff_Stove & switchon_Microwave", "score": "1.6108384"}, {"id": "182", "title": "Check if the stove is off before turning on the kettle.", "text": "switchoff_Stove & switchon_Kettle", "score": "1.6019611"}, {"id": "122", "title": "Turn off the microwave and switch on the stove.", "text": "switchoff_Microwave & switchon_Stove", "score": "1.5633153"}]}
{"id": 29, "question": "Sit at the kitchen table and eat some salad.", "answer": "sit_Kitchentable & grab_Salad", "ctxs": [{"id": "135", "title": "Grab a plate and put it on the dining table next to the salad.", "text": "grab_Plate & put_Plate_DiningTable", "score": "1.7085502"}, {"id": "94", "title": "Take a seat at the kitchen table and enjoy your meal.", "text": "sit_Kitchentable", "score": "1.6629406"}, {"id": "44", "title": "Take a seat on the dining table and wait for the food to be served.", "text": "sit_DiningTable", "score": "1.391256"}]}
{"id": 30, "question": "If the wall TV is off, switch it on using the remote.", "answer": "lookat_WallTV & switchon_WallTV", "ctxs": [{"id": "113", "title": "Touch the wall TV and switch on the wall phone.", "text": "touch_WallTV & switchon_Wallphone", "score": "1.7604263"}, {"id": "68", "title": "Touch the shelf to turn off the wall lamps.", "text": "touch_Shelf", "score": "1.6707181"}, {"id": "177", "title": "Check if the cabinet is closed and the wall TV is switched on.", "text": "close_Cabinet & switchon_WallTV", "score": "1.6588924"}]}
{"id": 31, "question": "Take a pear from the fruit basket and wash it in the sink.", "answer": "grab_Pear & lookat_Sink", "ctxs": [{"id": "22", "title": "Grab a peach from the fruit basket on the counter.", "text": "grab_Peach", "score": "1.4516199"}, {"id": "199", "title": "If the wine glass is dirty, wash it; otherwise, put it in the sink.", "text": "lookat_WineGlass | putin_WineGlass_Fridge", "score": "1.3655424"}, {"id": "62", "title": "Grab an orange from the fruit bowl on the dining table.", "text": "grab_Orange", "score": "1.3441045"}]}
{"id": 32, "question": "Remember to close the microwave after taking out the roasted chicken.", "answer": "grab_Chicken & close_Microwave", "ctxs": [{"id": "5", "title": "Remember to close the microwave after taking out the roasted chicken.", "text": "close_Microwave", "score": "2.282707"}, {"id": "15", "title": "After using the microwave, remember to close the door.", "text": "close_Microwave", "score": "1.6580307"}, {"id": "85", "title": "Close the microwave after heating up the leftovers.", "text": "close_Microwave", "score": "1.6220007"}]}
{"id": 33, "question": "Open the microwave and remove the hot potato.", "answer": "open_Microwave & grab_Potato", "ctxs": [{"id": "85", "title": "Close the microwave after heating up the leftovers.", "text": "close_Microwave", "score": "1.3774453"}, {"id": "43", "title": "Open the microwave to see if the food is heated properly.", "text": "open_Microwave", "score": "1.3632601"}, {"id": "195", "title": "If the napkin is dirty, grab a fresh one; otherwise, check the potato in the fridge.", "text": "lookat_Napkin | lookat_Potato", "score": "1.3336712"}]}
{"id": 34, "question": "If the shelf is dusty, wipe it with a paper towel.", "answer": "lookat_Shelf & grab_PaperTowel", "ctxs": [{"id": "157", "title": "If the shelf is touched, switch off the dishwasher.", "text": "touch_Shelf & switchoff_Dishwasher", "score": "1.5014937"}, {"id": "117", "title": "Sit on the chair and touch the shelf.", "text": "sit_Chair & touch_Shelf", "score": "1.4775816"}, {"id": "68", "title": "Touch the shelf to turn off the wall lamps.", "text": "touch_Shelf", "score": "1.4137504"}]}
{"id": 35, "question": "Plug in the kettle and fill it with bottled water.", "answer": "switchon_Kettle & grab_Bottlewater", "ctxs": [{"id": "181", "title": "Grab a bottle of water from the fridge and put it on the dining table.", "text": "grab_Bottlewater & put_Bottlewater_DiningTable", "score": "1.4544348"}, {"id": "147", "title": "Make sure the kettle is unplugged and the toaster is switched off before you leave.", "text": "switchoff_Kettle & switchoff_Toaster", "score": "1.4510872"}, {"id": "112", "title": "If the stove is on, turn it off, or unplug the kettle.", "text": "switchoff_Stove | switchoff_Kettle", "score": "1.3858759"}]}
{"id": 36, "question": "Check if the bedroom light is on or the window is open.", "answer": "lookat_LightSwitch | open_Curtains", "ctxs": [{"id": "109", "title": "Check if the microwave door is closed or switch on the ceiling lamp.", "text": "close_Microwave | switchon_Ceilinglamp", "score": "1.6687264"}, {"id": "187", "title": "Before going to bed, check if the light switch is off and the microwave is inside the oven.", "text": "switchoff_LightSwitch & lookat_Microwave", "score": "1.5587871"}, {"id": "177", "title": "Check if the cabinet is closed and the wall TV is switched on.", "text": "close_Cabinet & switchon_WallTV", "score": "1.529509"}]}
{"id": 37, "question": "Put the dirty clothes in the washing machine and start it.", "answer": "putin_Clothes_Washingmachine & switchon_Washingmachine", "ctxs": [{"id": "46", "title": "Let's put the dirty dishbowls in the washing machine before they pile up.", "text": "putin_dishbowls_Washingmachine", "score": "1.61715"}, {"id": "16", "title": "Put the dirty dishes in the dishwasher before they pile up.", "text": "put_Dishbowl_Dishwasher", "score": "1.4660381"}, {"id": "66", "title": "Put the dirty dishes in the dishwasher, please.", "text": "putin_Dishbowl_Dishwasher", "score": "1.436954"}]}
{"id": 38, "question": "Turn left and enjoy a mug of hot chocolate to relax a bit.", "answer": "turn_left & drink_Mug", "ctxs": [{"id": "9", "title": "Enjoy a mug of hot beer to relax a bit.", "text": "drink_Beer", "score": "1.7676151"}, {"id": "67", "title": "Switch on the kettle for a cup of hot chocolate.", "text": "switchon_Kettle", "score": "1.354727"}, {"id": "59", "title": "How about having a sip of beer to relax?", "text": "drink_Beer", "score": "1.2573409"}]}
{"id": 39, "question": "If the cutlery knife is missing, take one from the drawer.", "answer": "~lookat_CutleryKnife | grab_CutleryKnife", "ctxs": [{"id": "23", "title": "Open the cabinet to get the cutlery knife for cutting.", "text": "open_Cabinet", "score": "1.6096686"}, {"id": "132", "title": "If the chef knife is on the shelf, grab it.", "text": "lookat_ChefKnife | grab_ChefKnife", "score": "1.3187523"}, {"id": "195", "title": "If the napkin is dirty, grab a fresh one; otherwise, check the potato in the fridge.", "text": "lookat_Napkin | lookat_Potato", "score": "1.2845669"}]}
{"id": 40, "question": "Adjust the wall picture frame and turn on the ceiling lamp.", "answer": "touch_WallPictureFrame & switchon_Ceilinglamp", "ctxs": [{"id": "58", "title": "Touch the wall to turn on the ceiling lamp.", "text": "touch_Ceilinglamp", "score": "1.8627207"}, {"id": "18", "title": "Touch the wall lamp to adjust the lighting in the room.", "text": "touch_Walllamp", "score": "1.8558794"}, {"id": "28", "title": "Touch the ceiling lamp to adjust the brightness in the room.", "text": "touch_Ceilinglamp", "score": "1.7917335"}]}
{"id": 41, "question": "Take an orange juice and sit on the dining chair.", "answer": "grab_Orange & sit_Chair", "ctxs": [{"id": "62", "title": "Grab an orange from the fruit bowl on the dining table.", "text": "grab_Orange", "score": "1.8181782"}, {"id": "44", "title": "Take a seat on the dining table and wait for the food to be served.", "text": "sit_DiningTable", "score": "1.6417956"}, {"id": "94", "title": "Take a seat at the kitchen table and enjoy your meal.", "text": "sit_Kitchentable", "score": "1.5506947"}]}
{"id": 42, "question": "If the dish towel is dirty, grab a clean napkin.", "answer": "~lookat_Napkin | grab_Napkin", "ctxs": [{"id": "195", "title": "If the napkin is dirty, grab a fresh one; otherwise, check the potato in the fridge.", "text": "lookat_Napkin | lookat_Potato", "score": "1.7988169"}, {"id": "26", "title": "Let's put the dirty plates in the dishwasher after dinner.", "text": "put_Plate_Dishwasher", "score": "1.5433488"}, {"id": "66", "title": "Put the dirty dishes in the dishwasher, please.", "text": "putin_Dishbowl_Dishwasher", "score": "1.4776936"}]}
{"id": 43, "question": "Close the dishwasher and check the fridge temperature.", "answer": "close_Dishwasher & lookat_Fridge", "ctxs": [{"id": "141", "title": "Check if the fridge door is closed, then switch on the light switch in the kitchen.", "text": "close_Fridge & switchon_LightSwitch", "score": "1.5726331"}, {"id": "175", "title": "If the dishwasher is open, close it, and turn on the microwave.", "text": "close_Dishwasher & switchon_Microwave", "score": "1.5715859"}, {"id": "108", "title": "If the fridge is open, close it, and switch off the toaster.", "text": "close_Fridge & switchoff_Toaster", "score": "1.564697"}]}
{"id": 44, "question": "If the kitchen table is cluttered, clear it immediately.", "answer": "lookat_Kitchentable & grab_Plate", "ctxs": [{"id": "36", "title": "Put the clean dishes in the cabinet before they get stacked up.", "text": "putin_Plate_Cabinet", "score": "1.4511209"}, {"id": "16", "title": "Put the dirty dishes in the dishwasher before they pile up.", "text": "put_Dishbowl_Dishwasher", "score": "1.4496043"}, {"id": "26", "title": "Let's put the dirty plates in the dishwasher after dinner.", "text": "put_Plate_Dishwasher", "score": "1.3114139"}]}
{"id": 45, "question": "Switch on the ceiling fan as it's getting a bit warm in here.", "answer": "walktowards_CeilingFan & switchon_CeilingFan", "ctxs": [{"id": "7", "title": "Switch on the ceiling fan as it's getting a bit warm in here.", "text": "switchon_CeilingFan", "score": "2.0401912"}, {"id": "161", "title": "Check if the fridge is closed and switch on the ceiling fan.", "text": "close_Fridge & switchon_CeilingFan", "score": "1.4992855"}, {"id": "188", "title": "Make sure the dishwasher is off before turning on the ceiling fan.", "text": "switchoff_Dishwasher & switchon_CeilingFan", "score": "1.4792767"}]}
{"id": 46, "question": "Put the cereal box back in the cabinet after use.", "answer": "open_Cabinet & putin_Cereal_Cabinet", "ctxs": [{"id": "76", "title": "Put the cereal box in the kitchen cabinet for storage.", "text": "put_Cereal_Cabinet", "score": "1.8155873"}, {"id": "13", "title": "Open the kitchen cabinet to get the cereal for breakfast.", "text": "open_Cabinet", "score": "1.446149"}, {"id": "194", "title": "Before preparing breakfast, check if the cereal box is empty or the milk carton is expired.", "text": "lookat_Cereal | lookat_Milk", "score": "1.381176"}]}
{"id": 47, "question": "If the bathroom light is on, switch it off.", "answer": "lookat_LightSwitch & switchoff_LightSwitch", "ctxs": [{"id": "138", "title": "If the wall lamp is off, switch it on; otherwise, touch the curtains.", "text": "switchoff_Walllamp | touch_Curtains", "score": "1.6436647"}, {"id": "190", "title": "If the wall lamp is on, switch it off; otherwise, close the fridge door.", "text": "switchoff_Walllamp | close_Fridge", "score": "1.5897269"}, {"id": "129", "title": "If the desk lamp is on, turn it off; otherwise, switch on the ceiling lamp.", "text": "switchoff_Desk & switchon_Ceilinglamp", "score": "1.544981"}]}
{"id": 48, "question": "Wipe the dining table with a damp cloth.", "answer": "grab_PaperTowel & lookat_DiningTable", "ctxs": [{"id": "26", "title": "Let's put the dirty plates in the dishwasher after dinner.", "text": "put_Plate_Dishwasher", "score": "1.3918463"}, {"id": "181", "title": "Grab a bottle of water from the fridge and put it on the dining table.", "text": "grab_Bottlewater & put_Bottlewater_DiningTable", "score": "1.357125"}, {"id": "16", "title": "Put the dirty dishes in the dishwasher before they pile up.", "text": "put_Dishbowl_Dishwasher", "score": "1.3474472"}]}
{"id": 49, "question": "If the sofa cushions are misplaced, arrange them properly.", "answer": "walktowards_Sofa & touch_Sofa", "ctxs": []}
{"id": 50, "question": "Put the dirty fork on the dining table and get a clean one.", "answer": "put_Cutleryfork_DiningTable & grab_Cutleryfork", "ctxs": [{"id": "26", "title": "Let's put the dirty plates in the dishwasher after dinner.", "text": "put_Plate_Dishwasher", "score": "1.6786304"}, {"id": "195", "title": "If the napkin is dirty, grab a fresh one; otherwise, check the potato in the fridge.", "text": "lookat_Napkin | lookat_Potato", "score": "1.5876632"}, {"id": "66", "title": "Put the dirty dishes in the dishwasher, please.", "text": "putin_Dishbowl_Dishwasher", "score": "1.5439503"}]}
{"id": 51, "question": "If the room is too bright, close the wall lamps.", "answer": "lookat_Walllamp & switchoff_Walllamp", "ctxs": [{"id": "68", "title": "Touch the shelf to turn off the wall lamps.", "text": "touch_Shelf", "score": "1.6787744"}, {"id": "18", "title": "Touch the wall lamp to adjust the lighting in the room.", "text": "touch_Walllamp", "score": "1.667673"}, {"id": "138", "title": "If the wall lamp is off, switch it on; otherwise, touch the curtains.", "text": "switchoff_Walllamp | touch_Curtains", "score": "1.64865"}]}
{"id": 52, "question": "Wipe the kitchen counter with a disinfectant spray.", "answer": "grab_PaperTowel & lookat_Kitchentable", "ctxs": [{"id": "157", "title": "If the shelf is touched, switch off the dishwasher.", "text": "touch_Shelf & switchoff_Dishwasher", "score": "1.2732668"}]}
{"id": 53, "question": "Grab a potato from the fridge for me, please.", "answer": "open_Fridge & grab_Potato", "ctxs": [{"id": "2", "title": "Grab a tomato from the fridge for me, please.", "text": "grab_Tomato", "score": "1.6254604"}, {"id": "195", "title": "If the napkin is dirty, grab a fresh one; otherwise, check the potato in the fridge.", "text": "lookat_Napkin | lookat_Potato", "score": "1.50471"}, {"id": "52", "title": "Please grab a banana from the kitchen.", "text": "grab_Banana", "score": "1.4217529"}]}
{"id": 54, "question": "Please close the cabinet.", "answer": "walktowards_Cabinet & close_Cabinet", "ctxs": [{"id": "168", "title": "If the door is open, please close it, or open it if it's closed.", "text": "close_Door | open_Door", "score": "1.4845755"}, {"id": "177", "title": "Check if the cabinet is closed and the wall TV is switched on.", "text": "close_Cabinet & switchon_WallTV", "score": "1.3489729"}]}
{"id": 55, "question": "How about sitting on the desk next to the window?", "answer": "walktowards_Desk & sit_Desk", "ctxs": [{"id": "4", "title": "How about sitting on the chair next to the window?", "text": "sit_Chair", "score": "2.1642175"}]}
{"id": 0, "question": "Turn left and grab the milk from the fridge", "answer": "turn_left & grab_Milk", "ctxs": [{"id": "186", "title": "Turn left and grab the Bread from the Fridge.", "text": "turn_left & grab_Bread", "score": "1.6559141"}, {"id": "65", "title": "Please grab a bottle of milk from the fridge for me.", "text": "grab_Milk", "score": "1.5115342"}, {"id": "13", "title": "Please close the fridge after getting the milk.", "text": "close_Fridge", "score": "1.4917233"}]}
{"id": 1, "question": "Open the window and switch off the ceiling lamp", "answer": "open_Window & switchoff_Ceilinglamp", "ctxs": [{"id": "182", "title": "Touch the Vase on the Shelf and switch off the Ceilinglamp.", "text": "touch_Vase & switchoff_Ceilinglamp", "score": "1.7185636"}, {"id": "155", "title": "Turn off the LightSwitch and switch on the Ceilinglamp in the room.", "text": "switchoff_LightSwitch & switchon_Ceilinglamp", "score": "1.7087281"}, {"id": "32", "title": "Turn on the wall lamp in the hallway.", "text": "switchon_Walllamp", "score": "1.6702774"}]}
{"id": 2, "question": "Need a new magazine to read, fetch one please", "answer": "walktowards_BookShelf & grab_Magazine", "ctxs": [{"id": "54", "title": "I need a new magazine to read. Can you grab one for me?", "text": "grab_Magazine", "score": "1.8192811"}]}
{"id": 3, "question": "If the beer is on the table, put it in the fridge", "answer": "put_Beer_Coffeetable | putin_Beer_Fridge", "ctxs": [{"id": "204", "title": "If you see the Beer on the Coffeetable, drink it or put it back in the Fridge.", "text": "drink_Beer | putin_Beer_Fridge", "score": "1.7952852"}, {"id": "207", "title": "If you see the Beer on the Counter, drink it or put it in the Fridge.", "text": "drink_Beer | putin_Beer_Fridge", "score": "1.7535923"}, {"id": "128", "title": "Check if the Beer is in the Fridge, drink it if it is there.", "text": "grab_Beer | putin_Beer_Fridge", "score": "1.7330924"}]}
{"id": 4, "question": "Check if the TV is on, if so turn it off", "answer": "~switchon_WallTV | switchoff_WallTV", "ctxs": [{"id": "107", "title": "Turn off the wall TV before we go to bed.", "text": "switchoff_WallTV", "score": "1.5754166"}, {"id": "180", "title": "If the Radio is on, turn it off; if not, switch on the WallTV.", "text": "switchoff_Radio | switchon_WallTV", "score": "1.5524951"}, {"id": "127", "title": "If the Powersocket is switched off, turn it on.", "text": "switchoff_Powersocket & switchon_Powersocket", "score": "1.5254953"}]}
{"id": 5, "question": "Take a left when you reach the computer", "answer": "walktowards_Computer & turn_left", "ctxs": [{"id": "43", "title": "When you enter the room, please turn right towards the computer.", "text": "turn_right", "score": "1.7743174"}, {"id": "40", "title": "Walk towards the computer on the desk.", "text": "walktowards_Computer", "score": "1.5225308"}, {"id": "52", "title": "Please turn left when you reach the end of the hallway.", "text": "turn_left", "score": "1.3910816"}]}
{"id": 6, "question": "Grab a wine bottle from the cabinet, would you?", "answer": "open_Cabinet & grab_Wine", "ctxs": [{"id": "53", "title": "Can you grab a bottle of wine from the wine cabinet for me?", "text": "grab_Wine", "score": "1.8361515"}, {"id": "73", "title": "Please grab a bottle of wine from the wine rack for me.", "text": "grab_Wine", "score": "1.6054156"}, {"id": "106", "title": "Let's have some wine with dinner, could you grab a bottle?", "text": "grab_Wine", "score": "1.5814252"}]}
{"id": 7, "question": "Bring me the magazine and a bottle of water", "answer": "grab_Magazine & grab_Bottlewater", "ctxs": [{"id": "81", "title": "Please grab a bottle of water from the fridge for me.", "text": "grab_Bottlewater", "score": "1.5470793"}, {"id": "96", "title": "Grab a bottle of water from the fridge for me, please.", "text": "grab_Bottlewater", "score": "1.5379645"}, {"id": "0", "title": "Can you please grab a bottle of water?", "text": "grab_Bottlewater", "score": "1.4926348"}]}
{"id": 8, "question": "Close the curtains and turn on the ceiling fan", "answer": "close_Curtains & switchon_CeilingFan", "ctxs": [{"id": "133", "title": "Turn off the CeilingFan and close the Curtains if they are open.", "text": "switchoff_CeilingFan & close_Curtains", "score": "1.996407"}, {"id": "219", "title": "Close the Curtains and switch on the CeilingFan.", "text": "close_Curtains & switchon_CeilingFan", "score": "1.9528933"}, {"id": "39", "title": "Turn off the fan on the ceiling.", "text": "switchoff_CeilingFan", "score": "1.9247534"}]}
{"id": 9, "question": "Toss the empty chips bag in the trash after snacking", "answer": "grab_Chips & putin_Chips_Garbagecan", "ctxs": [{"id": "51", "title": "After you finish your snack, could you put the empty chips bag in the garbage can?", "text": "putin_Chips_Garbagecan", "score": "2.062635"}, {"id": "145", "title": "If the Chips are on the Couch, either grab them or put them in the Garbagecan.", "text": "grab_Chips | putin_Chips_Garbagecan", "score": "1.6192952"}, {"id": "214", "title": "If the Chips are on the Counter, grab them; otherwise, put them in the Box.", "text": "grab_Chips | putin_Chips_Box", "score": "1.4671862"}]}
{"id": 10, "question": "Deal the cards on the table", "answer": "put_Cards_Coffeetable", "ctxs": []}
{"id": 11, "question": "Don't forget to close the microwave before leaving", "answer": "close_Microwave", "ctxs": [{"id": "49", "title": "Before leaving, please remember to close the microwave.", "text": "close_Microwave", "score": "2.1344056"}, {"id": "76", "title": "Before you leave, please close the door behind you.", "text": "close_Door", "score": "1.5322816"}, {"id": "55", "title": "Before we leave, please remember to switch off the WallTV.", "text": "switchoff_WallTV", "score": "1.4144182"}]}
{"id": 12, "question": "Is the hair product open?", "answer": "lookat_HairProduct & open_HairProduct", "ctxs": []}
{"id": 13, "question": "Drink water and put the bottle on the nightstand", "answer": "drink_Bottlewater & put_Bottlewater_Nightstand", "ctxs": [{"id": "202", "title": "Grab a Bottlewater from the Fridge and drink it or put it in the Microwave.", "text": "grab_Bottlewater | putin_Bottlewater_Microwave", "score": "1.6171458"}, {"id": "125", "title": "Find the Clock on the Nightstand and touch it.", "text": "lookat_Clock & touch_Clock", "score": "1.4808834"}, {"id": "36", "title": "Walk towards the nightstand in the bedroom.", "text": "walktowards_Nightstand", "score": "1.4703405"}]}
{"id": 14, "question": "Turn on the printer and grab a pen", "answer": "switchon_Printer & grab_Pen", "ctxs": [{"id": "192", "title": "Walk towards the Computer and grab a Pen if it's available.", "text": "walktowards_Computer & grab_Pen", "score": "1.6271125"}, {"id": "172", "title": "Walk towards the Clock and grab the Pen.", "text": "walktowards_Clock & grab_Pen", "score": "1.5967019"}, {"id": "208", "title": "Make sure the Radio is switched off and grab the Pen from the BookShelf.", "text": "switchoff_Radio & grab_Pen", "score": "1.5320785"}]}
{"id": 15, "question": "Just sit on the TV stand", "answer": "walktowards_TVstand & sit_TVstand", "ctxs": [{"id": "23", "title": "Walk towards the TV stand in the living room.", "text": "walktowards_TVstand", "score": "1.8480765"}, {"id": "63", "title": "Can you walk towards the TV stand in the living room?", "text": "walktowards_TVstand", "score": "1.8047954"}, {"id": "3", "title": "Could you turn off the TV at the stand?", "text": "switchoff_TVstand", "score": "1.7525902"}]}
{"id": 16, "question": "Grab that chef knife quickly", "answer": "open_Drawer & grab_ChefKnife", "ctxs": [{"id": "171", "title": "Make sure the ChefKnife is on the Kitchen counter; if not, grab the Spoon from the Drawer.", "text": "grab_ChefKnife | grab_Spoon", "score": "1.5646768"}, {"id": "217", "title": "Grab the ChefKnife from the Drawer and put it on the Coffeetable.", "text": "grab_ChefKnife | put_ChefKnife_Coffeetable", "score": "1.5361292"}, {"id": "115", "title": "Grab a spoon from the drawer for the soup.", "text": "grab_Spoon", "score": "1.2681079"}]}
{"id": 17, "question": "Store the board game on shelf", "answer": "grab_Boardgame & put_Boardgame_BookShelf", "ctxs": [{"id": "104", "title": "Can you grab a toy from the shelf for the kids to play with?", "text": "grab_Toy", "score": "1.2712133"}]}
{"id": 18, "question": "Either put the chicken in microwave or switch it off", "answer": "putin_Chicken_Microwave | switchoff_Microwave", "ctxs": [{"id": "141", "title": "If you see the chicken on the Plate, either eat it or put it in the Microwave.", "text": "grab_Chicken | putin_Chicken_Microwave", "score": "1.6918943"}, {"id": "98", "title": "Open the microwave to heat up the leftovers.", "text": "open_Microwave", "score": "1.350846"}, {"id": "174", "title": "Open the Microwave and put the Plate inside it.", "text": "open_Microwave & putin_Plate_Microwave", "score": "1.3450708"}]}
{"id": 19, "question": "Turn right and touch the photo frame", "answer": "turn_right & touch_PhotoFrame", "ctxs": [{"id": "142", "title": "Switch on the LightSwitch if it's off and touch the PhotoFrame on the Wall.", "text": "switchoff_LightSwitch & touch_PhotoFrame", "score": "1.6120718"}, {"id": "68", "title": "Can you walk towards the photo frame on the wall?", "text": "walktowards_PhotoFrame", "score": "1.5414698"}, {"id": "218", "title": "Walk towards the PhotoFrame and open the Fridge.", "text": "walktowards_PhotoFrame & open_Fridge", "score": "1.5374966"}]}
{"id": 20, "question": "I need a towel from the bathroom, put it in the washer", "answer": "putin_Towel_Washingmachine", "ctxs": [{"id": "45", "title": "I need a towel from the bathroom. Can you put it in the washing machine for me?", "text": "putin_Towel_Washingmachine", "score": "1.7653987"}, {"id": "83", "title": "Please grab a towel from the bathroom.", "text": "grab_Towel", "score": "1.6289926"}, {"id": "9", "title": "Grab a towel from the laundry basket.", "text": "grab_Towel", "score": "1.5905893"}]}
{"id": 21, "question": "It's too bright, mind turning off the ceiling lamp?", "answer": "switchoff_Ceilinglamp", "ctxs": [{"id": "46", "title": "It's too bright in here. Can you turn off the ceiling lamp?", "text": "switchoff_Ceilinglamp", "score": "1.8538129"}, {"id": "71", "title": "It's too dark in here. Could you switch on the wall lamp?", "text": "switchon_Walllamp", "score": "1.5294542"}, {"id": "118", "title": "It's getting hot in here, can you turn on the ceiling lamp?", "text": "switchon_Ceilinglamp", "score": "1.439861"}]}
{"id": 22, "question": "Drink the milk and put the mug on the coffeetable", "answer": "drink_Milk & put_Mug_Coffeetable", "ctxs": [{"id": "16", "title": "Walk towards the coffee table and grab a mug.", "text": "walktowards_Coffeetable", "score": "1.6521866"}, {"id": "74", "title": "After you finish your drink, could you put the mug in the dishwasher?", "text": "putin_Mug_Dishwasher", "score": "1.6001261"}, {"id": "124", "title": "Open the cabinet and grab a mug for the coffee.", "text": "open_Cabinet", "score": "1.5671403"}]}
{"id": 23, "question": "Take the salad from the fridge and put on the plate", "answer": "grab_Salad & put_Salad_Plate", "ctxs": [{"id": "103", "title": "Put the salad back in the fridge after you finish your meal.", "text": "putin_Salad_Fridge", "score": "1.743275"}, {"id": "178", "title": "If there is a Salad on the Counter, grab it; if not, grab the Chips.", "text": "grab_Salad | grab_Chips", "score": "1.344727"}, {"id": "62", "title": "I need a tomato for the salad. Can you grab one from the fridge?", "text": "grab_Tomato", "score": "1.328332"}]}
{"id": 24, "question": "Can you grab that water bottle from the fridge?", "answer": "open_Fridge & grab_Bottlewater", "ctxs": [{"id": "48", "title": "Could you grab the bottle of water from the fridge, please?", "text": "grab_Bottlewater", "score": "2.0738533"}, {"id": "96", "title": "Grab a bottle of water from the fridge for me, please.", "text": "grab_Bottlewater", "score": "1.8295255"}, {"id": "81", "title": "Please grab a bottle of water from the fridge for me.", "text": "grab_Bottlewater", "score": "1.7973623"}]}
{"id": 25, "question": "Switch off the radio or turn on the projector", "answer": "switchoff_Radio | switchon_Projector", "ctxs": [{"id": "151", "title": "Turn off the Radio and switch on the Projector.", "text": "switchoff_Radio & switchon_Projector", "score": "2.3547688"}, {"id": "89", "title": "Turn on the projector for the presentation.", "text": "switchon_Projector", "score": "1.8156999"}, {"id": "11", "title": "Turn on the projector for the presentation.", "text": "switchon_Projector", "score": "1.8156999"}]}
{"id": 26, "question": "Close the dishwasher and open the window", "answer": "close_Dishwasher & open_Window", "ctxs": [{"id": "197", "title": "Switch off the Powersocket and close the Window in the Living Room.", "text": "switchoff_Powersocket & close_Window", "score": "1.5418167"}, {"id": "183", "title": "Walk towards the Window and close it if it's open.", "text": "walktowards_Window & close_Window", "score": "1.4872236"}, {"id": "147", "title": "Walk towards the Window and close it if it's open.", "text": "walktowards_Window & close_Window", "score": "1.4872236"}]}
{"id": 27, "question": "Please grab an apple from the kitchen counter", "answer": "walktowards_Coffeetable & grab_Apple", "ctxs": [{"id": "44", "title": "Please grab an apple from the kitchen for me.", "text": "grab_Apple", "score": "2.0177567"}, {"id": "90", "title": "Please grab an apple from the fruit bowl.", "text": "grab_Apple", "score": "1.8676225"}, {"id": "33", "title": "Grab a fresh apple from the fruit bowl.", "text": "grab_Apple", "score": "1.6407108"}]}
{"id": 28, "question": "I think I left my pen on the desk, could you check?", "answer": "lookat_Pen", "ctxs": [{"id": "47", "title": "I believe I left my pen on the desk. Could you check it for me?", "text": "lookat_Pen", "score": "2.0579877"}, {"id": "72", "title": "I believe I left my spoon on the table. Can you look at it for me?", "text": "lookat_Spoon", "score": "1.3638206"}, {"id": "85", "title": "I need a pen from the drawer, can you grab it for me?", "text": "grab_Pen", "score": "1.3589051"}]}
{"id": 29, "question": "Either sit on the sofa or turn on the TV", "answer": "sit_Sofa | switchon_WallTV", "ctxs": [{"id": "1", "title": "Let's sit on the sofa.", "text": "walktowards_Sofa", "score": "1.6451485"}, {"id": "166", "title": "Turn off the TVstand and grab the TeddyBear from the Sofa.", "text": "switchoff_TVstand & grab_TeddyBear", "score": "1.5406013"}, {"id": "107", "title": "Turn off the wall TV before we go to bed.", "text": "switchoff_WallTV", "score": "1.5397253"}]}
{"id": 30, "question": "Grab the toothpaste and put in the cabinet", "answer": "grab_Toothpaste & putin_Toothpaste_Cabinet", "ctxs": [{"id": "143", "title": "Walk towards the Chair and grab the Toothbrush on it.", "text": "walktowards_Chair & grab_Toothbrush", "score": "1.4301244"}, {"id": "124", "title": "Open the cabinet and grab a mug for the coffee.", "text": "open_Cabinet", "score": "1.3454921"}, {"id": "171", "title": "Make sure the ChefKnife is on the Kitchen counter; if not, grab the Spoon from the Drawer.", "text": "grab_ChefKnife | grab_Spoon", "score": "1.2887267"}]}
{"id": 31, "question": "Take a banana from the coffeetable", "answer": "walktowards_Coffeetable & grab_Banana", "ctxs": [{"id": "159", "title": "If there are Chips on the Coffeetable, grab them; otherwise, eat a Banana.", "text": "grab_Chips | grab_Banana", "score": "1.8726647"}, {"id": "188", "title": "Grab the Pear from the Fruit Bowl and put it on the Coffeetable.", "text": "grab_Pear | put_Pear_Coffeetable", "score": "1.5471196"}, {"id": "179", "title": "Turn right and grab the Apple on the Coffeetable.", "text": "turn_right & grab_Apple", "score": "1.5326194"}]}
{"id": 32, "question": "Turn left and look at the bookshelf", "answer": "turn_left & lookat_BookShelf", "ctxs": [{"id": "19", "title": "Look at the book on the bookshelf.", "text": "lookat_Book", "score": "1.9153336"}, {"id": "82", "title": "Can you take a look at the bookshelf?", "text": "lookat_BookShelf", "score": "1.8183359"}, {"id": "7", "title": "Walk towards the bookshelf in the living room.", "text": "walktowards_BookShelf", "score": "1.7599277"}]}
{"id": 33, "question": "Unplug the power socket", "answer": "switchoff_Powersocket", "ctxs": [{"id": "24", "title": "Turn off the power socket next to the computer.", "text": "switchoff_Powersocket", "score": "1.6853629"}, {"id": "99", "title": "Turn off the power socket, we're not using it right now.", "text": "switchoff_Powersocket", "score": "1.6450927"}, {"id": "127", "title": "If the Powersocket is switched off, turn it on.", "text": "switchoff_Powersocket & switchon_Powersocket", "score": "1.3826717"}]}
{"id": 34, "question": "Could you walk toward the bookshelf for me?", "answer": "walktowards_BookShelf & lookat_BookShelf", "ctxs": [{"id": "42", "title": "Can you walk toward the bookshelf for me?", "text": "walktowards_BookShelf", "score": "2.312425"}, {"id": "7", "title": "Walk towards the bookshelf in the living room.", "text": "walktowards_BookShelf", "score": "1.8153446"}, {"id": "78", "title": "Could you walk towards the clock on the wall for me?", "text": "walktowards_Clock", "score": "1.7008415"}]}
{"id": 35, "question": "Put the wine bottle in the fridge or on the table", "answer": "putin_Wine_Fridge | put_Wine_Coffeetable", "ctxs": [{"id": "20", "title": "Please put the wine bottle on the coffee table.", "text": "put_Wine_Coffeetable", "score": "1.7928374"}, {"id": "153", "title": "If the Wine is on the Counter, either grab it or put it in the Fridge.", "text": "grab_Wine | putin_Wine_Fridge", "score": "1.7165387"}, {"id": "194", "title": "If you see the Bottlewater on the Coffeetable, drink it or put it in the Fridge.", "text": "drink_Bottlewater | putin_Bottlewater_Fridge", "score": "1.5453287"}]}
{"id": 36, "question": "Remember to turn off the wall TV before bed", "answer": "walktowards_WallTV & switchoff_WallTV", "ctxs": [{"id": "107", "title": "Turn off the wall TV before we go to bed.", "text": "switchoff_WallTV", "score": "2.1509342"}, {"id": "55", "title": "Before we leave, please remember to switch off the WallTV.", "text": "switchoff_WallTV", "score": "1.7922628"}, {"id": "94", "title": "Turn off the TV stand before we head out.", "text": "switchoff_TVstand", "score": "1.6233565"}]}
{"id": 37, "question": "My phone's missing, check the nightstand", "answer": "open_Nightstand & lookat_Cellphone", "ctxs": [{"id": "56", "title": "I need to find my cellphone. Can you check on the nightstand for me?", "text": "lookat_Cellphone", "score": "1.7568119"}, {"id": "64", "title": "I need to find my keys. Could you look at the nightstand?", "text": "lookat_Nightstand", "score": "1.5012639"}, {"id": "116", "title": "Walk towards the nightstand, my phone is charging there.", "text": "walktowards_Nightstand", "score": "1.4796962"}]}
{"id": 38, "question": "Head over to the sofa in the living room", "answer": "walktowards_Sofa & sit_Sofa", "ctxs": [{"id": "57", "title": "Please walk towards the sofa in the living room.", "text": "walktowards_Sofa", "score": "1.7134321"}, {"id": "30", "title": "Walk towards the window in the living room.", "text": "walktowards_Window", "score": "1.4846992"}, {"id": "7", "title": "Walk towards the bookshelf in the living room.", "text": "walktowards_BookShelf", "score": "1.4341749"}]}
{"id": 39, "question": "Can't find my book, look at the bookshelf", "answer": "walktowards_BookShelf & lookat_Book", "ctxs": [{"id": "19", "title": "Look at the book on the bookshelf.", "text": "lookat_Book", "score": "1.9182067"}, {"id": "82", "title": "Can you take a look at the bookshelf?", "text": "lookat_BookShelf", "score": "1.817663"}, {"id": "58", "title": "I can't find my favorite book. Could you look at the bookshelf?", "text": "lookat_Book", "score": "1.7386475"}]}
{"id": 40, "question": "Grab a beer from the fridge, will you?", "answer": "open_Fridge & grab_Beer", "ctxs": [{"id": "22", "title": "Grab a bottle of beer from the fridge.", "text": "grab_Beer", "score": "1.8102857"}, {"id": "59", "title": "Can you grab a bottle of beer from the fridge for me?", "text": "grab_Beer", "score": "1.7382495"}, {"id": "101", "title": "Grab a beer from the fridge, it's time to relax.", "text": "grab_Beer", "score": "1.6242713"}]}
{"id": 41, "question": "Too noisy, turn off the radio please", "answer": "walktowards_Radio & switchoff_Radio", "ctxs": [{"id": "84", "title": "Turn off the radio, it's too loud.", "text": "switchoff_Radio", "score": "2.0119805"}, {"id": "60", "title": "It's too noisy in here. Can you turn off the radio?", "text": "switchoff_Radio", "score": "1.9086651"}, {"id": "14", "title": "Turn off the music on the radio.", "text": "switchoff_Radio", "score": "1.6465714"}]}
{"id": 42, "question": "Make a right at the coffeetable ahead", "answer": "walktowards_Coffeetable & turn_right", "ctxs": [{"id": "179", "title": "Turn right and grab the Apple on the Coffeetable.", "text": "turn_right & grab_Apple", "score": "1.7025125"}, {"id": "138", "title": "Walk towards the Apple on the Coffeetable and eat it.", "text": "walktowards_Apple & grab_Apple", "score": "1.4082692"}, {"id": "206", "title": "Walk toward the Window and close it if it's open, then touch the Vase on the Coffeetable.", "text": "walktowards_Window & close_Window", "score": "1.3992467"}]}
{"id": 43, "question": "Need a tomato for salad, fridge has some", "answer": "open_Fridge & grab_Tomato", "ctxs": [{"id": "62", "title": "I need a tomato for the salad. Can you grab one from the fridge?", "text": "grab_Tomato", "score": "1.8660619"}, {"id": "37", "title": "Grab a fresh tomato from the vegetable basket.", "text": "grab_Tomato", "score": "1.4125289"}, {"id": "103", "title": "Put the salad back in the fridge after you finish your meal.", "text": "putin_Salad_Fridge", "score": "1.3637733"}]}
{"id": 44, "question": "Switch off the ceiling fan and close the window", "answer": "switchoff_CeilingFan & close_Window", "ctxs": [{"id": "133", "title": "Turn off the CeilingFan and close the Curtains if they are open.", "text": "switchoff_CeilingFan & close_Curtains", "score": "1.8730967"}, {"id": "219", "title": "Close the Curtains and switch on the CeilingFan.", "text": "close_Curtains & switchon_CeilingFan", "score": "1.8674728"}, {"id": "39", "title": "Turn off the fan on the ceiling.", "text": "switchoff_CeilingFan", "score": "1.838676"}]}
{"id": 45, "question": "Turn off the radio and turn left", "answer": "switchoff_Radio & turn_left", "ctxs": [{"id": "14", "title": "Turn off the music on the radio.", "text": "switchoff_Radio", "score": "1.690424"}, {"id": "187", "title": "Switch off the WallTV and turn right.", "text": "switchoff_WallTV | turn_right", "score": "1.5527505"}, {"id": "158", "title": "Turn off the Radio and look at the Clock on the wall.", "text": "switchoff_Radio & lookat_Clock", "score": "1.5322274"}]}
{"id": 46, "question": "Walk towards the desk and touch the WallPictureFrame above it", "answer": "walktowards_Desk & touch_WallPictureFrame", "ctxs": [{"id": "163", "title": "Walk towards the Chair and touch the WallPictureFrame above it.", "text": "walktowards_Chair & touch_WallPictureFrame", "score": "2.262806"}, {"id": "200", "title": "Ensure the WallPictureFrame is turned off and then open the Window beside it.", "text": "switchoff_WallPictureFrame & open_Window", "score": "1.8112559"}, {"id": "40", "title": "Walk towards the computer on the desk.", "text": "walktowards_Computer", "score": "1.6904135"}]}
{"id": 47, "question": "Take the potato from the drawer", "answer": "open_Drawer & grab_Potato", "ctxs": [{"id": "168", "title": "Open the Garbagecan and put the Potato inside.", "text": "open_Garbagecan & putin_Potato_Garbagecan", "score": "1.4903607"}, {"id": "115", "title": "Grab a spoon from the drawer for the soup.", "text": "grab_Spoon", "score": "1.4385312"}, {"id": "41", "title": "Please grab a pen from the drawer.", "text": "grab_Pen", "score": "1.4218605"}]}
{"id": 48, "question": "Put the magazine on the nightstand", "answer": "grab_Magazine & put_Magazine_Nightstand", "ctxs": [{"id": "91", "title": "Put the magazine back on the coffee table when you're done reading.", "text": "put_Magazine_Coffeetable", "score": "1.6347914"}, {"id": "137", "title": "Locate the Magazine on the Coffeetable and grab it.", "text": "walktowards_Coffeetable & grab_Magazine", "score": "1.6011353"}, {"id": "205", "title": "Turn on the LightSwitch and look at the Magazine on the Coffeetable.", "text": "switchoff_LightSwitch & lookat_Magazine", "score": "1.5519546"}]}
{"id": 49, "question": "Touch the teddy bear and turn right", "answer": "touch_TeddyBear & turn_right", "ctxs": [{"id": "173", "title": "If you see the TeddyBear on the Nightstand, touch it or turn left.", "text": "touch_TeddyBear | turn_left", "score": "1.5414146"}, {"id": "126", "title": "Walk towards the Sofa and grab the TeddyBear.", "text": "walktowards_Sofa & grab_TeddyBear", "score": "1.3065635"}, {"id": "187", "title": "Switch off the WallTV and turn right.", "text": "switchoff_WallTV | turn_right", "score": "1.2997018"}]}
{"id": 50, "question": "Open the microwave and take out the chicken", "answer": "open_Microwave & grab_Chicken", "ctxs": [{"id": "141", "title": "If you see the chicken on the Plate, either eat it or put it in the Microwave.", "text": "grab_Chicken | putin_Chicken_Microwave", "score": "1.6230037"}, {"id": "174", "title": "Open the Microwave and put the Plate inside it.", "text": "open_Microwave & putin_Plate_Microwave", "score": "1.4713072"}, {"id": "215", "title": "Close the Microwave and grab the Spoon from the Drawer.", "text": "close_Microwave & grab_Spoon", "score": "1.444859"}]}
{"id": 51, "question": "Look at the computer screen", "answer": "walktowards_Computer & lookat_CPUscreen", "ctxs": [{"id": "176", "title": "Look at the Computer and drink the Beer next to it.", "text": "lookat_Computer & drink_Beer", "score": "1.5666351"}, {"id": "19", "title": "Look at the book on the bookshelf.", "text": "lookat_Book", "score": "1.5487903"}, {"id": "38", "title": "Look at the painting on the wall.", "text": "lookat_WallPictureFrame", "score": "1.4934897"}]}
{"id": 52, "question": "When you enter the room, please turn right toward the computer and touch it", "answer": "turn_right & touch_Computer", "ctxs": [{"id": "43", "title": "When you enter the room, please turn right towards the computer.", "text": "turn_right", "score": "2.4681764"}, {"id": "40", "title": "Walk towards the computer on the desk.", "text": "walktowards_Computer", "score": "1.664504"}, {"id": "52", "title": "Please turn left when you reach the end of the hallway.", "text": "turn_left", "score": "1.540483"}]}